<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ramblings on IntangibleMatter</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/tags/ramblings/</link><description>Recent content in Ramblings on IntangibleMatter</description><generator>Hugo 0.125.2</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 09:25:27 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://intangiblematter.github.io/tags/ramblings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fuck It, It's All Me</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2024/01/27/fuck-it-its-all-me/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 08:16:37 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2024/01/27/fuck-it-its-all-me/</guid><description>For the past few months I&amp;rsquo;ve had my blog separated into two different pages: /posts/ and /personal/. Posts was where my more general, public-friendly stuff would go, and personal is my archive for all my personal ramblings. But you know what, fuck it. It&amp;rsquo;s all me. Every post on here is me, whether it&amp;rsquo;s a personal rambling or it&amp;rsquo;s a guide on how to do something in tech. It&amp;rsquo;s all me.</description></item><item><title>Don Hertzfeldt, Hangar, and the Desire to Be Human</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/07/16/don-hertzfeldt-hangar-and-the-desire-to-be-human/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 00:01:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/07/16/don-hertzfeldt-hangar-and-the-desire-to-be-human/</guid><description>So if you&amp;rsquo;ve spent any amount of time talking to me (or, more accurately, listening to me talk,) you&amp;rsquo;ve probably heard me talk about Don Hertzfeldt. Don Hertzfeldt is a self-described Oscar-losing filmmaker. He makes animated films starring stick figures, dry narration, and some of the most beautiful stories I&amp;rsquo;ve ever seen. His debut feature, It&amp;rsquo;s Such A Beautiful Day, is an hour-long attack on the senses, featuring filmmaking techniques taken to their limits.</description></item><item><title>The Rare Moments You Feel Like You're Real</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/06/08/the-rare-moments-you-feel-like-youre-real/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 00:10:38 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/06/08/the-rare-moments-you-feel-like-youre-real/</guid><description>Here&amp;#39;s a song that I like. Might be good to listen to with this post. Idk.
You know how some people feel like they&amp;rsquo;re the only real person in the world?
I have the opposite problem.
To some degree.
Society paints a very strong picture in our minds of what a &amp;ldquo;teenager&amp;rdquo; is supposed to do. And I very rarely find myself meeting those expectations. Whether it&amp;rsquo;s because of my anxiety, depression, or just general tendencies to isolate myself socially (lockdown was a bit of a dream come true), I tend to find myself working on my computer, browsing the internet, and just being alone with my (admittedly distressing) thoughts.</description></item><item><title>My First Fullindie Meetup</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/06/06/my-first-fullindie-meetup/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 23:27:46 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/06/06/my-first-fullindie-meetup/</guid><description>So&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;m writing this on the ferry ride home from my very first FullIndie meetup! I basically got on a bus right after school to get down to the ferry, then I went into Vancouer and&amp;hellip; ate food?
Also all of this was with my friend River. They&amp;rsquo;re cool. Check them out. Without whom I probably would&amp;rsquo;ve been having an anxiety attack for the whole trip so&amp;hellip; thanks, Riv!
After we ate, we went down to the Skytrain and went down to the place where the meetup was happening.</description></item><item><title>Mirrors</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/02/23/mirrors/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 13:59:16 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/02/23/mirrors/</guid><description>I feel like the people we get along best with are always, to some degree, mirrors of ourselves. My closest friends all mirror some aspect of myself, and I some aspect of them. The more you mirror, the more likely you are to be friends.
A lot of my friends don&amp;rsquo;t have much in common, aside from being generally smart in various ways, and always having something or another that they can talk your ear off about.</description></item></channel></rss>