<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fanboying on IntangibleMatter</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/fanboying/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fanboying on IntangibleMatter</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 09:25:27 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/fanboying/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Wallsocket</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/09/26/wallsocket/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 08:56:10 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/09/26/wallsocket/</guid>
      <description>Wallsocket, the new album released by underscores on September 22nd, 2023, has quickly and easily risen to be my album of the year. After a lead up of a variety of singles being released, almost all of which I greatly enjoyed, the album released with a great variety of genres, tones, themes, and characters, all while feeling like a very cohesive work.&#xA;Cops and Robbers pass&#xA;Locals (Girls like us) pass</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s the New Wave of the Future!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/06/10/its-the-new-wave-of-the-future/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 08:25:02 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/06/10/its-the-new-wave-of-the-future/</guid>
      <description>My music taste changes constantly. I had a long time where I mostly listened to video game music, then a good few months where I mostly listened to electro. (Thanks, Just Shapes and Beats!) Recently, though, I&amp;rsquo;ve been listening to hyperpop. For those of you who don&amp;rsquo;t know, hyperpop is a musical genre which can be loosely defined as a type of music that borrows strongly from pop for its layout, early 2000s internet for its musical aesthetics, and pretty much whatever the hell the artist feels like for the lyrics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Katana ZERO Is a Masterpiece</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/05/15/katana-zero-is-a-masterpiece/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 13:05:35 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/05/15/katana-zero-is-a-masterpiece/</guid>
      <description>Katana ZERO, for those of you who don&amp;rsquo;t know, is a 2019 video game created by Justin Standard (aka Askiisoft) and a few others. It features difficult side-scrolling action, tight combat, an amazing soundtrack, beautiful pixel art, and one of my favourite stories of the past decade. While I could rave about it for hours, I&amp;rsquo;ll do my best to keep this article finite.&#xA;Also, in case it wasn&amp;rsquo;t obvious, there will be MAJOR SPOILERS for Katana ZERO!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Owl House Was Special</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/04/08/the-owl-house-was-special/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 16:38:12 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/04/08/the-owl-house-was-special/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m writing this article as I&amp;rsquo;m finishing The Owl House series finale, something I&amp;rsquo;ve been waiting for for a few years now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Brief Hantiplad About Everything Everywhere All At Once</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/03/22/a-brief-hantiplad-about-everything-everywhere-all-at-once/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 00:51:09 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/03/22/a-brief-hantiplad-about-everything-everywhere-all-at-once/</guid>
      <description>So I finally got to watch that movie everyone was talking about last year. It&amp;rsquo;s honestly even better than everyone says. The effects were amazing, the writing was fantastic, and the actors were all&amp;hellip; *chef&amp;rsquo;s kiss*.&#xA;Our deadpan-hyper chaotic-evil queen.&#xA;My favourite character was easily Jobu Tupekai. She&amp;rsquo;s honestly everything I aspire to be. A cool, nihilistic, reality warping, amazing looking young adult who created an object that can destroy the most powerful people somewhat out of boredom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wandersong and Oddballism</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/03/05/wandersong-and-oddballism/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 14:28:59 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/03/05/wandersong-and-oddballism/</guid>
      <description>Wandersong is a very special game. Ask almost anyone who&amp;rsquo;s played it, and you&amp;rsquo;ll find them at the very least agreeing enthusiastically, and more than likely raving about some moment in the game or another. In addition to this, the creator says there&amp;rsquo;s almost as many pieces of fanart as copies of the game sold. Which is, to put it lightly, incredible. But I&amp;rsquo;m not here today to talk about how beloved this game is.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daria and the Reality of High School, Or Why I Never Hang Out With My Friends</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/03/03/daria-and-the-reality-of-high-school-or-why-i-never-hang-out-with-my-friends/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:24:48 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/03/03/daria-and-the-reality-of-high-school-or-why-i-never-hang-out-with-my-friends/</guid>
      <description>Daria, for those of you who don&amp;rsquo;t know, is a late-90s tv show which aired on MTV. It is also the single most accurate depiction of my high school experience that I have seen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Games Most Important to Me</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/02/23/the-games-most-important-to-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 22:55:46 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/02/23/the-games-most-important-to-me/</guid>
      <description>In case you couldn&amp;rsquo;t tell by the fact that I make games and have spent the majority of the money I&amp;rsquo;ve gotten as a teenager on Steam gift cards, I&amp;rsquo;m a bit of a fan of the medium of video games.&#xA;The Beginner&amp;rsquo;s Guide Everybody feels like shit sometimes.&#xA;Everybody makes mistakes.&#xA;Not everybody makes a game which conveys these feelings so effectively and in a way that feels so painfully accurate to how it feels to have hurt somebody in a way you can&amp;rsquo;t take back.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
