<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Technical on IntangibleMatter</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/technical/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Technical on IntangibleMatter</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 09:25:27 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/technical/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Make a Screenspace Visualshader in Godot</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2024/01/25/how-to-make-a-screenspace-visualshader-in-godot/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 11:10:12 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2024/01/25/how-to-make-a-screenspace-visualshader-in-godot/</guid>
      <description>Click here to skip to the instructions.&#xA;So Godot Engine has a really cool shader system, allowing you to do stuff like change the way lighting works in both 2D and 3D using nothing but shaders, and it additionally has a powerful VisualShader system. VisualShaders, for those who don&amp;rsquo;t know, are shaders that use a Shader Graph system instead of pure code. I&amp;rsquo;m not huge on node-based programming systems, so I usually elect to (poorly) write a shader myself, but I&amp;rsquo;m working on a game jam with a larger team than I ever have before right now, and they wanted to use the ShaderV addon because of how many cool things it has.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECDL a New File Type for ECS Engines</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/12/23/ecdl-a-new-file-type-for-ecs-engines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 14:39:25 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/12/23/ecdl-a-new-file-type-for-ecs-engines/</guid>
      <description>ECDL, Or Entity Component Definition Language, is a new Markup Language (Technically two) designed for Defining Entities and Components in Entity Component Systems, but more specifically the new engine I&amp;rsquo;ve started work on both against my better judgment and the advice of friends. ECDL can be split into two different markup languages that write quite similarly. Let&amp;rsquo; start with what I consider the simpler of the two.&#xA;EDL - Entity Definition Language EDL, or Entity Definition Language, is used for, well, defining entities.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
