<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>IntangibleMatter</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on IntangibleMatter</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 19:00:30 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>YAUFYAITG</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2024/03/02/yaufyaitg/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 00:34:03 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2024/03/02/yaufyaitg/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re wondering what the title stands for, it&amp;rsquo;s Yet Another Update From Yet Another Internet Trans Girl, and this post is exactly what it says on the tin.&#xA;I have some posts about my previous gender questioning on this page, so it&amp;rsquo;s not anything new. But tl;dr for anyone who hasn&amp;rsquo;t read the previous posts: I&amp;rsquo;m gender questioning, fit a lot of tropes for transfems, spend a ton of time thinking about what it would be like to be a girl, wishing I was a girl, knowing that girls (especially trans ones) have a lot harder time moving through life than cis guys do, but still feeling like it would be easier, etc, etc, etc.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fuck It, It&#39;s All Me</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2024/01/27/fuck-it-its-all-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 08:16:37 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2024/01/27/fuck-it-its-all-me/</guid>
      <description>For the past few months I&amp;rsquo;ve had my blog separated into two different pages: /posts/ and /personal/. Posts was where my more general, public-friendly stuff would go, and personal is my archive for all my personal ramblings. But you know what, fuck it. It&amp;rsquo;s all me. Every post on here is me, whether it&amp;rsquo;s a personal rambling or it&amp;rsquo;s a guide on how to do something in tech. It&amp;rsquo;s all me.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Make a Screenspace Visualshader in Godot</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2024/01/25/how-to-make-a-screenspace-visualshader-in-godot/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 11:10:12 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2024/01/25/how-to-make-a-screenspace-visualshader-in-godot/</guid>
      <description>Click here to skip to the instructions.&#xA;So Godot Engine has a really cool shader system, allowing you to do stuff like change the way lighting works in both 2D and 3D using nothing but shaders, and it additionally has a powerful VisualShader system. VisualShaders, for those who don&amp;rsquo;t know, are shaders that use a Shader Graph system instead of pure code. I&amp;rsquo;m not huge on node-based programming systems, so I usually elect to (poorly) write a shader myself, but I&amp;rsquo;m working on a game jam with a larger team than I ever have before right now, and they wanted to use the ShaderV addon because of how many cool things it has.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECDL a New File Type for ECS Engines</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/12/23/ecdl-a-new-file-type-for-ecs-engines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 14:39:25 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/12/23/ecdl-a-new-file-type-for-ecs-engines/</guid>
      <description>ECDL, Or Entity Component Definition Language, is a new Markup Language (Technically two) designed for Defining Entities and Components in Entity Component Systems, but more specifically the new engine I&amp;rsquo;ve started work on both against my better judgment and the advice of friends. ECDL can be split into two different markup languages that write quite similarly. Let&amp;rsquo; start with what I consider the simpler of the two.&#xA;EDL - Entity Definition Language EDL, or Entity Definition Language, is used for, well, defining entities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECS vs OOP, or Why I Will Never be Happy With a Game Engine</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/12/18/ecs-vs-oop-or-why-i-will-never-be-happy-with-a-game-engine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 08:24:31 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/12/18/ecs-vs-oop-or-why-i-will-never-be-happy-with-a-game-engine/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carol Dontlookup and Media After Covid</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/12/17/carol-dontlookup-and-media-after-covid/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 02:20:36 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/12/17/carol-dontlookup-and-media-after-covid/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Favourites of 2023</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/12/17/my-favourites-of-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 02:19:45 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/12/17/my-favourites-of-2023/</guid>
      <description>As 2023 comes to a close, everyone is writing their lists of The Top 10 Games of 2023, or The Best Albums of the Year or whatever other miscellaneous things you can make lists of. So I decided to write something about the media I enjoyed this year, if nothing else for the sake of the Permanent Record of the Internet™ (and myself) to look back upon. I could separate this by the type of media, order it by my favourite, but I think it&amp;rsquo;ll be easiest if I just order by when I first experienced them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Beginner&#39;s Guide to File Management</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/11/15/the-beginners-guide-to-file-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 02:57:11 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/11/15/the-beginners-guide-to-file-management/</guid>
      <description>So, it has come to my attention as of late that most people my age and younger were never taught how to properly organize their files. As someone born in 2006, I grew up on Windows XP, so I was forced to learn how to organize files, or else my entire computer would be a mess. I got more training later through my life thanks to my dad&amp;rsquo;s (who I called &amp;lsquo;Lala&amp;rsquo;) excellent file organization, and the face that in order to be effective in game development you need an effective folder structure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You Can&#39;t Fight the Homestuck</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/10/30/you-cant-fight-the-homestuck/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 11:03:28 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/10/30/you-cant-fight-the-homestuck/</guid>
      <description>In August of this year I started reading one of the most infamous webcomics, parts of internet culture, and just general clusterfucks out there. Which is to say that I started reading Homestuck.&#xA;Homestuck, for those who don&amp;rsquo;t know, is/was a webcomic about four kids who play a game that results in the end of the world, and their efforts to create a new one. That&amp;rsquo;s the short version of it, and it also mentions nothing of the numerous flashes, incredible music, odd spin-offs and sidequests, its nature as a borderline cult, much to the distress of the creator, and all of the other chaos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wallsocket</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/09/26/wallsocket/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 08:56:10 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/09/26/wallsocket/</guid>
      <description>Wallsocket, the new album released by underscores on September 22nd, 2023, has quickly and easily risen to be my album of the year. After a lead up of a variety of singles being released, almost all of which I greatly enjoyed, the album released with a great variety of genres, tones, themes, and characters, all while feeling like a very cohesive work.&#xA;Cops and Robbers pass&#xA;Locals (Girls like us) pass</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antisocial Media</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/09/14/antisocial-media/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 09:47:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/09/14/antisocial-media/</guid>
      <description>Social media sucks.&#xA;Wow, groundbreaking opinion, right?&#xA;Seriously, though. The kinds of platforms which the entire modern internet are based on are horrible in so many ways. There&amp;rsquo;s the fact they&amp;rsquo;re designed to addict, the way they&amp;rsquo;re used to spy on people, and just the general horrible way data gets treated by these platforms. I have, unless stated otherwise, used all of the following platforms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plague Town</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/08/24/plague-town/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 05:13:25 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/08/24/plague-town/</guid>
      <description>Plague Town by 8485 is an incredibly special album to me.&#xA;While I started out listening to only one or two songs from it, over the next year it always had a song that was exactly what I needed when I needed it, and I slowly added all five songs on the EP to my rotation. From the longing, echoing synths of Hangar to the lying on the floor breakup song Southview, there was always something special in this album for me.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Installing Fmod Studio on Pop!_OS</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/08/03/installing-fmod-studio-on-pop_os/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 01:27:58 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/08/03/installing-fmod-studio-on-pop_os/</guid>
      <description>So, as a game developer, I love FMOD. Advanced sound is always so cool to me! However, when installing FMOD Studio on Pop!_OS, you&amp;rsquo;ll run into an issue.&#xA;$ dpkg -i fmodstudio&amp;lt;version&amp;gt;.deb Package pulseaudio is not installed So, even though it requires a bit of editing files that you probably shouldn&amp;rsquo;t, it&amp;rsquo;s actually quite easy!&#xA;First, run dpkg -i --force-all fmodstudio&amp;lt;version&amp;gt;.deb. This installs FMOD Studio, and FMOD Studio will run just fine!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barbie and the Council of 2000</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/07/23/barbie-and-the-council-of-2000/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 00:04:14 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/07/23/barbie-and-the-council-of-2000/</guid>
      <description>So I watched Barbie with some friends, and it was really good! I loved the storytelling, the characters, the plot, and&amp;hellip; god dammit, I wasn&amp;rsquo;t expecting a Barbie movie to be the most unabashedly feminist work I&amp;rsquo;d ever seen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don Hertzfeldt, Hangar, and the Desire to Be Human</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/07/16/don-hertzfeldt-hangar-and-the-desire-to-be-human/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 00:01:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/07/16/don-hertzfeldt-hangar-and-the-desire-to-be-human/</guid>
      <description>So if you&amp;rsquo;ve spent any amount of time talking to me (or, more accurately, listening to me talk,) you&amp;rsquo;ve probably heard me talk about Don Hertzfeldt. Don Hertzfeldt is a self-described Oscar-losing filmmaker. He makes animated films starring stick figures, dry narration, and some of the most beautiful stories I&amp;rsquo;ve ever seen. His debut feature, It&amp;rsquo;s Such A Beautiful Day, is an hour-long attack on the senses, featuring filmmaking techniques taken to their limits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hangar</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/06/12/hangar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 11:20:26 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/06/12/hangar/</guid>
      <description>If you held me against a wall with a gun to my head asking me what my favourite song was, I&amp;rsquo;d probably have a fatal panic attack.&#xA;If I somehow managed to respond, however, I would probably say with very little hesitation that the answer is Hangar by 8485. It&amp;rsquo;s a song that means a lot to me, and that I&amp;rsquo;ve listened to more times than any other song in my music library.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s the New Wave of the Future!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/06/10/its-the-new-wave-of-the-future/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 08:25:02 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/06/10/its-the-new-wave-of-the-future/</guid>
      <description>My music taste changes constantly. I had a long time where I mostly listened to video game music, then a good few months where I mostly listened to electro. (Thanks, Just Shapes and Beats!) Recently, though, I&amp;rsquo;ve been listening to hyperpop. For those of you who don&amp;rsquo;t know, hyperpop is a musical genre which can be loosely defined as a type of music that borrows strongly from pop for its layout, early 2000s internet for its musical aesthetics, and pretty much whatever the hell the artist feels like for the lyrics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Rare Moments You Feel Like You&#39;re Real</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/06/08/the-rare-moments-you-feel-like-youre-real/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 00:10:38 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/06/08/the-rare-moments-you-feel-like-youre-real/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;#39;s a song that I like. Might be good to listen to with this post. Idk.&#xA;You know how some people feel like they&amp;rsquo;re the only real person in the world?&#xA;I have the opposite problem.&#xA;To some degree.&#xA;Society paints a very strong picture in our minds of what a &amp;ldquo;teenager&amp;rdquo; is supposed to do. And I very rarely find myself meeting those expectations. Whether it&amp;rsquo;s because of my anxiety, depression, or just general tendencies to isolate myself socially (lockdown was a bit of a dream come true), I tend to find myself working on my computer, browsing the internet, and just being alone with my (admittedly distressing) thoughts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My First Fullindie Meetup</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/06/06/my-first-fullindie-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 23:27:46 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/06/06/my-first-fullindie-meetup/</guid>
      <description>So&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;m writing this on the ferry ride home from my very first FullIndie meetup! I basically got on a bus right after school to get down to the ferry, then I went into Vancouer and&amp;hellip; ate food?&#xA;Also all of this was with my friend River. They&amp;rsquo;re cool. Check them out. Without whom I probably would&amp;rsquo;ve been having an anxiety attack for the whole trip so&amp;hellip; thanks, Riv!&#xA;After we ate, we went down to the Skytrain and went down to the place where the meetup was happening.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impostor Syndrome, Adhd, and Burgers</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/05/31/impostor-syndrome-adhd-and-burgers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 12:24:11 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/05/31/impostor-syndrome-adhd-and-burgers/</guid>
      <description>So this is just a short little update. At the time of writing this, I&amp;rsquo;m currently waiting for a burger because I have nothing better to do in the time between now and when I go and talk to a whole bunch of mental health people to find out if my mental illness is disruptive enough to the system to give me support for something that I&amp;rsquo;ve recently realized has been making my whole life harder than it has to be.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s a Defence Mechanism</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/05/29/its-a-defence-mechanism/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 15:58:59 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/05/29/its-a-defence-mechanism/</guid>
      <description>I can be a bit of a dick sometimes, and I&amp;rsquo;m well aware. I don&amp;rsquo;t want to be, I frequently don&amp;rsquo;t even mean to be, but, almost as a reflex, I am. I exist almost in a state of perpetual vulnerability.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Perfect Mac and Cheese (According to My Dead Dad)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/05/27/the-perfect-mac-and-cheese-according-to-my-dead-dad/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 22:35:26 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/05/27/the-perfect-mac-and-cheese-according-to-my-dead-dad/</guid>
      <description>My dad (or as I and my family called him, Lala,) had a lot of experience with making mac and cheese from a box. While he had cancer, he ate a lot of mac and cheese because most foods didn&amp;rsquo;t taste good to him because of all the stuff in his body to fight the cancer. One day, when he was too tired to make it himself, he told me how he always makes it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eggs Like Russian Dolls</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/05/23/eggs-like-russian-dolls/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 15:28:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/05/23/eggs-like-russian-dolls/</guid>
      <description>So a while back I made a post about how my egg had cracked, and that I was, disappointingly, cis.&#xA;In retrospect, I now think that the egg had just cracked to reveal another egg. I just kind of default to being cis because it&amp;rsquo;s what i know, and because I feel uncomfortable with uncertainty, especially about core parts of myself. I don&amp;rsquo;t think any truly cis person could say the phrase &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m cis in the way that I&amp;rsquo;d do lines of estrogen&amp;rdquo; with a straight face.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oops! All Parasocial!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/05/23/oops-all-parasocial/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 10:50:45 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/05/23/oops-all-parasocial/</guid>
      <description>So&amp;hellip; it&amp;rsquo;s not exactly a secret that I&amp;rsquo;ve struggled to make friendships in life. I&amp;rsquo;ve never been good at reading social signals, I&amp;rsquo;m always direct about things that most people are at least somewhat awkward about, and I&amp;rsquo;ve always had a lot of niche intrests that most people I know knew little to nothing about. On top of that, I have social anxiety! Which for me means that obviously someone not replying for a while means that I made a social misstep that I didn&amp;rsquo;t notice and not that they&amp;rsquo;re busy or something.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Katana ZERO Is a Masterpiece</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/05/15/katana-zero-is-a-masterpiece/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 13:05:35 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/05/15/katana-zero-is-a-masterpiece/</guid>
      <description>Katana ZERO, for those of you who don&amp;rsquo;t know, is a 2019 video game created by Justin Standard (aka Askiisoft) and a few others. It features difficult side-scrolling action, tight combat, an amazing soundtrack, beautiful pixel art, and one of my favourite stories of the past decade. While I could rave about it for hours, I&amp;rsquo;ll do my best to keep this article finite.&#xA;Also, in case it wasn&amp;rsquo;t obvious, there will be MAJOR SPOILERS for Katana ZERO!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Heat Is Horrible</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/05/15/the-heat-is-horrible/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 08:25:40 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/05/15/the-heat-is-horrible/</guid>
      <description>So&amp;hellip; it&amp;rsquo;s mid May and the temperature has suddenly shot up by about 10 degrees where I live. If you lived in Ontario or something, this would probably be normal, but I live in southwest BC. The temperature getting above or below 8-12 degrees is weird, especially this suddenly. Or I guess it isn&amp;rsquo;t weird, just miserable. Another sucky part of it is that my town isn&amp;rsquo;t frequently this hot so most buildings don&amp;rsquo;t have air conditioning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Footpedal: A FOSS Audio Engine for Games</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/05/12/footpedal-a-foss-audio-engine-for-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 10:01:10 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/05/12/footpedal-a-foss-audio-engine-for-games/</guid>
      <description>I love dynamic audio in games. Being a game developer, I want to add it to my own projects. Unfortunately, I&amp;rsquo;m broke and all existing solutions are expensive to use (at least without a giant splash screen when you boot up the game.) Obviously, being a programmer myself, I decided I&amp;rsquo;d try to write an audio engine on my own. This is, of course, a completely giant task, and I am not amazing at programming complex systems, especially at lower levels, so I pretty much gave up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m Fine: a Short Film</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/05/05/im-fine-a-short-film/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 00:10:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/05/05/im-fine-a-short-film/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m Fine is a short film that I wrote, recorded, and filmed almost entirely by myself in late April of 2023 for my high school&amp;rsquo;s film fest. I&amp;rsquo;ve had ideas for various projects about my mental health for a few years now. This is the first project of this vein that I&amp;rsquo;ve completed, and it almost definitely won&amp;rsquo;t be the last. This film features me and three representations of various aspects of my mental health while anxiety screams over me, depression mopes while resting its head on the heater, and my own expectations of myself frantically justify why they exist by the mirror.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You&#39;ve Cracked Your Egg, Now Fry in It</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/04/28/youve-cracked-your-egg-now-fry-in-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 00:45:36 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/04/28/youve-cracked-your-egg-now-fry-in-it/</guid>
      <description>A while back I made a post about my gender and my experience in questioning. I&amp;rsquo;m happy to announce that my egg has recently cracked! And&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;m not trans.&#xA;Disappointing, right? I know, I was disappointed too. But it&amp;rsquo;s fine to not be a member of a group with so many cool members oh my god it&amp;rsquo;s statistically anomalous how many cool trans people there are. What I am, however, is someone who doesn&amp;rsquo;t strongly identify with the societal construct of masculinity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>That One Person Who Presses All the Buttons</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/04/26/that-one-person-who-presses-all-the-buttons/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 19:12:24 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/04/26/that-one-person-who-presses-all-the-buttons/</guid>
      <description>Do you have that one person who just somehow perfectly presses the buttons on all of your insecurities without even knowing it? That person who just seems so untouchable and perfect that their mere existence seems like some cosmic joke at your expense? Even if you know they&amp;rsquo;re still human, and that they also deal with issues like humans do, it just feels like they&amp;rsquo;ve figured out a method for hiding all of their struggles perfectly?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comments</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/04/17/comments/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 15:58:35 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/04/17/comments/</guid>
      <description>Hey! You might notice something new down at the bottom of my blog posts. It&amp;rsquo;s a comments section! You can leave comments on my ramblings if you have a Github account and you sign in to it.&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;m using a system called giscus for my comments. It means I don&amp;rsquo;t have to worry about self-hosting anything, and I can just use github! Specifically, Github discussions, which is a way for people to talk about a repo on the site, and it means that I don&amp;rsquo;t need to handle anyone&amp;rsquo;s data myself!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Owl House Was Special</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/04/08/the-owl-house-was-special/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 16:38:12 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/04/08/the-owl-house-was-special/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m writing this article as I&amp;rsquo;m finishing The Owl House series finale, something I&amp;rsquo;ve been waiting for for a few years now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eggs and Gender</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/03/28/eggs-and-gender/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 09:10:26 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/03/28/eggs-and-gender/</guid>
      <description>Gender is weird.&#xA;It&amp;rsquo;s such a social construct yet our society has been built on it on such a fundamental level that to most it&amp;rsquo;s a huge deal for most people to even consider changing from the gender they&amp;rsquo;ve been assigned. It&amp;rsquo;s an even bigger deal because of all the genocidal language that&amp;rsquo;s getting thrown around by neofascists about trans people as of late.&#xA;Which, of course, means it&amp;rsquo;s a great time to resume the questioning I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing on and off for the last 5 years!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Brief Hantiplad About Everything Everywhere All At Once</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/03/22/a-brief-hantiplad-about-everything-everywhere-all-at-once/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 00:51:09 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/03/22/a-brief-hantiplad-about-everything-everywhere-all-at-once/</guid>
      <description>So I finally got to watch that movie everyone was talking about last year. It&amp;rsquo;s honestly even better than everyone says. The effects were amazing, the writing was fantastic, and the actors were all&amp;hellip; *chef&amp;rsquo;s kiss*.&#xA;Our deadpan-hyper chaotic-evil queen.&#xA;My favourite character was easily Jobu Tupekai. She&amp;rsquo;s honestly everything I aspire to be. A cool, nihilistic, reality warping, amazing looking young adult who created an object that can destroy the most powerful people somewhat out of boredom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wandersong and Oddballism</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/03/05/wandersong-and-oddballism/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 14:28:59 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/03/05/wandersong-and-oddballism/</guid>
      <description>Wandersong is a very special game. Ask almost anyone who&amp;rsquo;s played it, and you&amp;rsquo;ll find them at the very least agreeing enthusiastically, and more than likely raving about some moment in the game or another. In addition to this, the creator says there&amp;rsquo;s almost as many pieces of fanart as copies of the game sold. Which is, to put it lightly, incredible. But I&amp;rsquo;m not here today to talk about how beloved this game is.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daria and the Reality of High School, Or Why I Never Hang Out With My Friends</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/03/03/daria-and-the-reality-of-high-school-or-why-i-never-hang-out-with-my-friends/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:24:48 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/03/03/daria-and-the-reality-of-high-school-or-why-i-never-hang-out-with-my-friends/</guid>
      <description>Daria, for those of you who don&amp;rsquo;t know, is a late-90s tv show which aired on MTV. It is also the single most accurate depiction of my high school experience that I have seen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Would It Kill Them to Declare a Snow Day</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/02/28/would-it-kill-them-to-declare-a-snow-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 07:15:03 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/02/28/would-it-kill-them-to-declare-a-snow-day/</guid>
      <description>It is 7:15 am right now. The snow on the road outside my house is currently about 15cm deep at least and shows no signs of slowing down. I wake up, look out my window and assume they&amp;rsquo;ve declared a snow day. Checking my school&amp;rsquo;s app, however, tells me a different story.&#xA;Dear [my school district] Learning Community: All [my school district] schools will have a DELAYED START today, Tuesday, February 28, 2023, due to inclement weather.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Games Most Important to Me</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/02/23/the-games-most-important-to-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 22:55:46 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/02/23/the-games-most-important-to-me/</guid>
      <description>In case you couldn&amp;rsquo;t tell by the fact that I make games and have spent the majority of the money I&amp;rsquo;ve gotten as a teenager on Steam gift cards, I&amp;rsquo;m a bit of a fan of the medium of video games.&#xA;The Beginner&amp;rsquo;s Guide Everybody feels like shit sometimes.&#xA;Everybody makes mistakes.&#xA;Not everybody makes a game which conveys these feelings so effectively and in a way that feels so painfully accurate to how it feels to have hurt somebody in a way you can&amp;rsquo;t take back.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mirrors</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/02/23/mirrors/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 13:59:16 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/02/23/mirrors/</guid>
      <description>I feel like the people we get along best with are always, to some degree, mirrors of ourselves. My closest friends all mirror some aspect of myself, and I some aspect of them. The more you mirror, the more likely you are to be friends.&#xA;A lot of my friends don&amp;rsquo;t have much in common, aside from being generally smart in various ways, and always having something or another that they can talk your ear off about.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don Hertzfeldt and the Meaning of Death</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/02/22/don-hertzfeldt-and-the-meaning-of-death/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 20:55:44 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/02/22/don-hertzfeldt-and-the-meaning-of-death/</guid>
      <description>Don Hertzfeldt, if you haven&amp;rsquo;t heard of him, is a filmmaker with a simple yet distinct art style. His works It&amp;rsquo;s Such a Beautiful Day and the World of Tomorrow series are some of the most</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test Post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/01/17/test-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 11:09:46 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/01/17/test-post/</guid>
      <description>This post is just here so my blog isn&amp;rsquo;t empty&#xA;Definitely deleting it soon.&#xA;Bye :)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Game Engines [ARCHIVE]</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2021/07/12/game-engines-archive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 10:01:29 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2021/07/12/game-engines-archive/</guid>
      <description>PLEASE NOTE: this is an archive from my original blog. It was my only post.&#xA;Before we begin: A game engine is a tool which is used to create games. It usually has a user interface and a scripting language (a specialized programming language unique to the engine) of some sort. A game _framework_ is a library of code which can be added to your code so it&amp;#39;s easier to make a game.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Looking for Personal?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2006/01/03/looking-for-personal/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2006 17:58:58 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2006/01/03/looking-for-personal/</guid>
      <description>Hey there!&#xA;Looking for the personal posts on my blog?&#xA;Just click the link below!&#xA;intangiblematter.net/posts/</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
