<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Update on IntangibleMatter</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/tags/update/</link><description>Recent content in Update on IntangibleMatter</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 19:42:57 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://intangiblematter.github.io/tags/update/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fuck It, It's All Me</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2024/01/27/fuck-it-its-all-me/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 08:16:37 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2024/01/27/fuck-it-its-all-me/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;For the past few months I&amp;rsquo;ve had my blog separated into two different pages:
&lt;code&gt;/posts/&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;/personal/&lt;/code&gt;. Posts was where my more general, public-friendly
stuff would go, and personal is my archive for all my personal ramblings. But
you know what, fuck it. It&amp;rsquo;s all me. Every post on here is me, whether it&amp;rsquo;s a
personal rambling or it&amp;rsquo;s a guide on how to do something in tech. It&amp;rsquo;s all me.
If you just want one, you can go ahead and use the two links at the top to
filter your experience. But this site is me, so everything on it is me. I&amp;rsquo;m not
going to pretend like I&amp;rsquo;m partitioned off into differrent people.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Eggs Like Russian Dolls</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/05/23/eggs-like-russian-dolls/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 15:28:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/05/23/eggs-like-russian-dolls/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;So &lt;a href="https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/04/28/youve-cracked-your-egg-now-fry-in-it/"&gt;a while back&lt;/a&gt;
I made a post about how my egg had cracked, and that I was, disappointingly,
cis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In retrospect, I now think that the egg had just cracked to reveal another egg.
I just kind of default to being cis because it&amp;rsquo;s what i know, and because I
feel uncomfortable with uncertainty, especially about core parts of myself.
I don&amp;rsquo;t think any &lt;em&gt;truly&lt;/em&gt; cis person could say the phrase &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m cis in the way
that I&amp;rsquo;d do lines of estrogen&amp;rdquo; with a straight face. Which is something that
I have done. Multiple times.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>You've Cracked Your Egg, Now Fry in It</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/04/28/youve-cracked-your-egg-now-fry-in-it/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 00:45:36 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/04/28/youve-cracked-your-egg-now-fry-in-it/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;A while back I &lt;a href="https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/03/28/eggs-and-gender/"&gt;made a post&lt;/a&gt; about
my gender and my experience in questioning. I&amp;rsquo;m happy to announce that my egg
has recently cracked! And&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;m not trans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Disappointing, right? I know, I was disappointed too. But it&amp;rsquo;s fine to not be
a member of a group with &lt;em&gt;so many cool members oh my god it&amp;rsquo;s statistically&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;em&gt;anomalous how many cool trans people there are.&lt;/em&gt; What I am, however, is
someone who doesn&amp;rsquo;t strongly identify with the societal construct of
masculinity. My dad didn&amp;rsquo;t either. ( Oh yeah, if you didn&amp;rsquo;t know, my dad, or as
I called him, Lala, died when I was 15 :/ ) He wore skirts a lot when I was
little and before I was born, he spent a lot of time wearing cool earings, and
he was a twice honorary lesbian, but that&amp;rsquo;s a story for another time. A lot of
his friends were women, and if societal gender was strictly determined by the
way you emotionally interact with the world, he would probably have been deemed
a woman. I feel like that&amp;rsquo;s where I sit. I myself am male, and I&amp;rsquo;m perfectly
comfortable with that. I just feel a lot more comfortable socially, and a lot
more comradery with afab people than I do with guys most of the time.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Comments</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/04/17/comments/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 15:58:35 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/04/17/comments/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Hey! You might notice something new down at the bottom of my blog posts. It&amp;rsquo;s a
comments section! You can leave comments on my ramblings if you have a Github
account and you sign in to it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m using a system called &lt;a href="https://giscus.app/"&gt;giscus&lt;/a&gt; for my comments. It means I
don&amp;rsquo;t have to worry about self-hosting anything, and I can just use github!
Specifically, Github discussions, which is a way for people to talk about a
repo on the site, and it means that I don&amp;rsquo;t need to handle anyone&amp;rsquo;s data
myself! If you don&amp;rsquo;t have a Github account, I highly encourage you to make one!
It&amp;rsquo;s a great community of people who make all sorts of cool open-source stuff,
and it&amp;rsquo;s free and secure enough that I use it to run my comments! If nothing
else, the ability to tell me why the comments section is a bad idea is a good
reason to sign up for Github and comment on this blog!&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Eggs and Gender</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/03/28/eggs-and-gender/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 09:10:26 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/03/28/eggs-and-gender/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Gender is weird.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s such a social construct yet our society has been built on it on such a
fundamental level that to most it&amp;rsquo;s a &lt;em&gt;huge&lt;/em&gt; deal for most people to even
&lt;em&gt;consider&lt;/em&gt; changing from the gender they&amp;rsquo;ve been assigned. It&amp;rsquo;s an even bigger
deal because of all the genocidal language that&amp;rsquo;s getting thrown around by
neofascists about trans people as of late.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Which, of course, means it&amp;rsquo;s a great time to resume the questioning I&amp;rsquo;ve been
doing on and off for the last 5 years! Totally not dangerous at all! (I mean,
it&amp;rsquo;s really not all thar dangerous for me, thankfully. I&amp;rsquo;m living in a rather
left-leaning community in Canada, which is generally considered one of the best
countries to be queer in. Unfortunately, right next door to the south is one of
the &lt;em&gt;worst&lt;/em&gt; countries to be trans in in the western world right now.
Republicans are using all sorts of rhetoric to try and villify them. The scary
part is that, for a lot of the conservatives in america, it&amp;rsquo;s &lt;em&gt;working&lt;/em&gt;. Fear
sells for a lot of people, and it&amp;rsquo;s hard to pull people out of it a lot of the
time.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>