<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>update on IntangibleMatter</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/tags/update/</link><description>Recent content in update on IntangibleMatter</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 09:25:27 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://intangiblematter.github.io/tags/update/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fuck It, It's All Me</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2024/01/27/fuck-it-its-all-me/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 08:16:37 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2024/01/27/fuck-it-its-all-me/</guid><description>For the past few months I&amp;rsquo;ve had my blog separated into two different pages: /posts/ and /personal/. Posts was where my more general, public-friendly stuff would go, and personal is my archive for all my personal ramblings. But you know what, fuck it. It&amp;rsquo;s all me. Every post on here is me, whether it&amp;rsquo;s a personal rambling or it&amp;rsquo;s a guide on how to do something in tech. It&amp;rsquo;s all me.</description></item><item><title>Eggs Like Russian Dolls</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/05/23/eggs-like-russian-dolls/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 15:28:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/05/23/eggs-like-russian-dolls/</guid><description>So a while back I made a post about how my egg had cracked, and that I was, disappointingly, cis.
In retrospect, I now think that the egg had just cracked to reveal another egg. I just kind of default to being cis because it&amp;rsquo;s what i know, and because I feel uncomfortable with uncertainty, especially about core parts of myself. I don&amp;rsquo;t think any truly cis person could say the phrase &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m cis in the way that I&amp;rsquo;d do lines of estrogen&amp;rdquo; with a straight face.</description></item><item><title>You've Cracked Your Egg, Now Fry in It</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/04/28/youve-cracked-your-egg-now-fry-in-it/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 00:45:36 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/04/28/youve-cracked-your-egg-now-fry-in-it/</guid><description>A while back I made a post about my gender and my experience in questioning. I&amp;rsquo;m happy to announce that my egg has recently cracked! And&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;m not trans.
Disappointing, right? I know, I was disappointed too. But it&amp;rsquo;s fine to not be a member of a group with so many cool members oh my god it&amp;rsquo;s statistically anomalous how many cool trans people there are. What I am, however, is someone who doesn&amp;rsquo;t strongly identify with the societal construct of masculinity.</description></item><item><title>Comments</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/04/17/comments/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 15:58:35 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/04/17/comments/</guid><description>Hey! You might notice something new down at the bottom of my blog posts. It&amp;rsquo;s a comments section! You can leave comments on my ramblings if you have a Github account and you sign in to it.
I&amp;rsquo;m using a system called giscus for my comments. It means I don&amp;rsquo;t have to worry about self-hosting anything, and I can just use github! Specifically, Github discussions, which is a way for people to talk about a repo on the site, and it means that I don&amp;rsquo;t need to handle anyone&amp;rsquo;s data myself!</description></item><item><title>Eggs and Gender</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/03/28/eggs-and-gender/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 09:10:26 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/03/28/eggs-and-gender/</guid><description>Gender is weird.
It&amp;rsquo;s such a social construct yet our society has been built on it on such a fundamental level that to most it&amp;rsquo;s a huge deal for most people to even consider changing from the gender they&amp;rsquo;ve been assigned. It&amp;rsquo;s an even bigger deal because of all the genocidal language that&amp;rsquo;s getting thrown around by neofascists about trans people as of late.
Which, of course, means it&amp;rsquo;s a great time to resume the questioning I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing on and off for the last 5 years!</description></item></channel></rss>