<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Short on IntangibleMatter</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/tags/short/</link><description>Recent content in Short on IntangibleMatter</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 19:42:57 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://intangiblematter.github.io/tags/short/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Eggs Like Russian Dolls</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/05/23/eggs-like-russian-dolls/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 15:28:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/05/23/eggs-like-russian-dolls/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;So &lt;a href="https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/04/28/youve-cracked-your-egg-now-fry-in-it/"&gt;a while back&lt;/a&gt;
I made a post about how my egg had cracked, and that I was, disappointingly,
cis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In retrospect, I now think that the egg had just cracked to reveal another egg.
I just kind of default to being cis because it&amp;rsquo;s what i know, and because I
feel uncomfortable with uncertainty, especially about core parts of myself.
I don&amp;rsquo;t think any &lt;em&gt;truly&lt;/em&gt; cis person could say the phrase &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m cis in the way
that I&amp;rsquo;d do lines of estrogen&amp;rdquo; with a straight face. Which is something that
I have done. Multiple times.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>You've Cracked Your Egg, Now Fry in It</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/04/28/youve-cracked-your-egg-now-fry-in-it/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 00:45:36 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/04/28/youve-cracked-your-egg-now-fry-in-it/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;A while back I &lt;a href="https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/03/28/eggs-and-gender/"&gt;made a post&lt;/a&gt; about
my gender and my experience in questioning. I&amp;rsquo;m happy to announce that my egg
has recently cracked! And&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;m not trans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Disappointing, right? I know, I was disappointed too. But it&amp;rsquo;s fine to not be
a member of a group with &lt;em&gt;so many cool members oh my god it&amp;rsquo;s statistically&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;em&gt;anomalous how many cool trans people there are.&lt;/em&gt; What I am, however, is
someone who doesn&amp;rsquo;t strongly identify with the societal construct of
masculinity. My dad didn&amp;rsquo;t either. ( Oh yeah, if you didn&amp;rsquo;t know, my dad, or as
I called him, Lala, died when I was 15 :/ ) He wore skirts a lot when I was
little and before I was born, he spent a lot of time wearing cool earings, and
he was a twice honorary lesbian, but that&amp;rsquo;s a story for another time. A lot of
his friends were women, and if societal gender was strictly determined by the
way you emotionally interact with the world, he would probably have been deemed
a woman. I feel like that&amp;rsquo;s where I sit. I myself am male, and I&amp;rsquo;m perfectly
comfortable with that. I just feel a lot more comfortable socially, and a lot
more comradery with afab people than I do with guys most of the time.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>That One Person Who Presses All the Buttons</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/04/26/that-one-person-who-presses-all-the-buttons/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 19:12:24 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/04/26/that-one-person-who-presses-all-the-buttons/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Do you have that one person who just somehow perfectly presses the buttons on
all of your insecurities without even knowing it? That person who just seems
so untouchable and perfect that their mere existence seems like some cosmic
joke at your expense? Even if you know they&amp;rsquo;re still human, and that they also
deal with issues like humans do, it just feels like they&amp;rsquo;ve figured out a
method for hiding all of their struggles perfectly?&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Mirrors</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/02/23/mirrors/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 13:59:16 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/02/23/mirrors/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;I feel like the people we get along best with are always, to some degree, mirrors of ourselves.
My closest friends all mirror some aspect of myself, and I some aspect of them. The more you mirror, the more likely you are to be friends.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A lot of my friends don&amp;rsquo;t have much in common, aside from being generally smart in various ways, and always having something or another that they can talk your ear off about.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>