<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>General on IntangibleMatter</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/tags/general/</link><description>Recent content in General on IntangibleMatter</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 15:44:28 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://intangiblematter.github.io/tags/general/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Reconciliation</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2024/06/17/reconciliation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 15:42:27 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2024/06/17/reconciliation/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;em>Note: This essay was written for an English First People&amp;rsquo;s Assignment, thank you.&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Reconciliation is an interesting topic.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>It&amp;rsquo;s also an &lt;em>incredibly&lt;/em> complicated one.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>For any of you in the audience who aren&amp;rsquo;t Canadian, Truth and Reconciliation is
an ongoing effort by the Government of Canada, and to varying degrees Canadian
citizens, to make amends for the horrors enacted upon the First Peoples of
Canada during colonization and the Residential School system. Its effectiveness
has been&amp;hellip; varied, but overall it&amp;rsquo;s doing the best work it can, considering
the circumstances.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Training for the Future</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2024/05/23/training-for-the-future/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 10:37:27 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2024/05/23/training-for-the-future/</guid><description>&lt;p>On Thursday, the 23rd of May, 2024, my high school psychology teacher claimed
that &amp;ldquo;the future started 2 days ago.&amp;rdquo; He was referring to GPT-4o and how
in another class of his several students came forward saying that, despite the
anti-AI measures that had been implemented in various courses, they still were
able to &amp;ldquo;cheat&amp;rdquo; with artificial intelligence and not be caught.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>While his lecture had several points, the core was this: AI is the future, and
we need to rule it so that it doesn&amp;rsquo;t rule us. Being a neophobe will hurt you
incredibly, and will ultimately leave you behind.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Who Cares If I End Up on the No-Fly List</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2024/05/01/who-cares-if-i-end-up-on-the-no-fly-list/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 01:16:25 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2024/05/01/who-cares-if-i-end-up-on-the-no-fly-list/</guid><description>&lt;p>Jesus Christ. Jesus &lt;em>&lt;strong>FUCKING&lt;/strong>&lt;/em> Christ.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The fact that this alt-right bullshit has made it to mainstream Canadian
politics is fucking &lt;em>terrifying.&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I&amp;rsquo;ve had an idea for a game kicking around in my head for a while now, something
commenting on the political situation in the world right now, &lt;em>specifically&lt;/em>
when it comes to transphobia.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Basic pitch is a stealth movement shooter where you assassinate prominent
anti-catgirl figures. Catgirls are definitely not acting as a stand in for
anything here, and you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t look into it further.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Fascism Litmus Test</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2024/03/19/fascism-litmus-test/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 10:31:29 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2024/03/19/fascism-litmus-test/</guid><description>&lt;p>As of writing, it has been 164 days since October 7th. In this time, we&amp;rsquo;ve seen
an alarming rise in antisemitism, an open genocide&amp;hellip;&lt;br>
And an &lt;em>upsetting&lt;/em> amount of people displaying how easy it is to sympathize with
fascism.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>As long as I&amp;rsquo;ve been politically aware, Israel has been&amp;hellip; a complicated topic.
On the one hand, yes there&amp;rsquo;s a lot of antisemitism in the world even today, and
it&amp;rsquo;s good to have a country where people can go that&amp;rsquo;s made so that they don&amp;rsquo;t
have to worry about it. On the other hand, well&amp;hellip;
&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nakba">it&amp;rsquo;s not like that land was free for use.&lt;/a>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How to Make a Screenspace Visualshader in Godot</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2024/01/25/how-to-make-a-screenspace-visualshader-in-godot/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 11:10:12 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2024/01/25/how-to-make-a-screenspace-visualshader-in-godot/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;a href="#the-actual-tutorial-bit-finally">&lt;em>Click here to skip to the instructions.&lt;/em>&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>So Godot Engine has a really cool shader system, allowing you to do stuff like
change the way lighting works in both 2D &lt;em>and&lt;/em> 3D using nothing but shaders,
and it additionally has a &lt;em>powerful&lt;/em> VisualShader system. VisualShaders, for
those who don&amp;rsquo;t know, are shaders that use a Shader Graph system instead of pure
code. I&amp;rsquo;m not huge on node-based programming systems, so I usually elect to
(poorly) write a shader myself, but I&amp;rsquo;m working on a game jam with a larger team
than I ever have before right now, and they wanted to use the &lt;a href="https://github.com/arkology/ShaderV">ShaderV addon&lt;/a>
because of how many cool things it has.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Installing Fmod Studio on Pop!_OS</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/08/03/installing-fmod-studio-on-pop_os/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 01:27:58 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/08/03/installing-fmod-studio-on-pop_os/</guid><description>&lt;p>So, as a game developer, I &lt;em>love&lt;/em> FMOD. Advanced sound is always so cool to me!
However, when installing FMOD Studio on Pop!_OS, you&amp;rsquo;ll run into an issue.&lt;/p>
&lt;div class="highlight">&lt;pre tabindex="0" style="color:#fff;background-color:#111;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;">&lt;code class="language-bash" data-lang="bash">&lt;span style="display:flex;">&lt;span>$ dpkg -i fmodstudio&amp;lt;version&amp;gt;.deb
&lt;/span>&lt;/span>&lt;span style="display:flex;">&lt;span>Package pulseaudio is not installed
&lt;/span>&lt;/span>&lt;/code>&lt;/pre>&lt;/div>&lt;p>So, even though it requires a &lt;em>bit&lt;/em> of editing files that you probably
shouldn&amp;rsquo;t, it&amp;rsquo;s actually quite easy!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>First, run &lt;code>dpkg -i --force-all fmodstudio&amp;lt;version&amp;gt;.deb&lt;/code>. This installs FMOD
Studio, and FMOD Studio will run just fine! There&amp;rsquo;s an issue, though.
When you next try to install something with &lt;code>apt&lt;/code> you&amp;rsquo;ll discover that it
won&amp;rsquo;t allow you to install anything, because a dependency is unresolved.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Perfect Mac and Cheese (According to My Dead Dad)</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/05/27/the-perfect-mac-and-cheese-according-to-my-dead-dad/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 22:35:26 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/05/27/the-perfect-mac-and-cheese-according-to-my-dead-dad/</guid><description>&lt;p>My dad (or as I and my family called him, Lala,) had a lot of experience with
making mac and cheese from a box. While he had cancer, he ate a lot of mac and
cheese because most foods didn&amp;rsquo;t taste good to him because of all the stuff in
his body to fight the cancer. One day, when he was too tired to make it
himself, he told me how he always makes it. He, quite honestly, made the best
box mac and cheese (and just straight up mac and cheese- I&amp;rsquo;m &lt;em>not&lt;/em> a fan of
the homemade stuff 99 times out of 100) I&amp;rsquo;ve ever tasted. Nostalgia bias?
Perhaps. But it&amp;rsquo;s still &lt;em>really&lt;/em> good, as it had about 55 years of perfection
under its belt.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Footpedal: A FOSS Audio Engine for Games</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/05/12/footpedal-a-foss-audio-engine-for-games/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 10:01:10 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/05/12/footpedal-a-foss-audio-engine-for-games/</guid><description>&lt;p>I &lt;em>love&lt;/em> dynamic audio in games. Being a game developer, I want to add it to my
own projects. Unfortunately, I&amp;rsquo;m broke and all existing solutions are expensive
to use (at least without a giant splash screen when you boot up the game.)
Obviously, being a programmer myself, I decided I&amp;rsquo;d try to write an audio
engine on my own. This is, of course, a completely giant task, and I am not
amazing at programming complex systems, especially at lower levels, so I
pretty much gave up. Before I gave up, though, I mentioned this project to a
friend of mine, &lt;a href="https://visu.do">River&lt;/a>, who promptly didn&amp;rsquo;t quite get it
and continued &lt;em>rewriting the JVM&lt;/em>. A few weeks back, though, they ended up
taking another look at the project, and we started working on it together.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>I'm Fine: a Short Film</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/05/05/im-fine-a-short-film/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 00:10:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/05/05/im-fine-a-short-film/</guid><description>&lt;div style="position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;">
 &lt;iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" loading="eager" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/nb-DMfLx_Kk?autoplay=0&amp;controls=1&amp;end=0&amp;loop=0&amp;mute=0&amp;start=0" style="position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;" title="YouTube video"
 >&lt;/iframe>
 &lt;/div>

&lt;p>&lt;em>I&amp;rsquo;m Fine&lt;/em> is a short film that I wrote, recorded, and filmed almost entirely
by myself in late April of 2023 for my high school&amp;rsquo;s film fest. I&amp;rsquo;ve had ideas
for various projects about my mental health for a few years now. This is the
first project of this vein that I&amp;rsquo;ve completed, and it almost definitely won&amp;rsquo;t
be the last. This film features me and three representations of various aspects
of my mental health while anxiety screams over me, depression mopes while
resting its head on the heater, and my own expectations of myself frantically
justify why they exist by the mirror.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Comments</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/04/17/comments/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 15:58:35 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/04/17/comments/</guid><description>&lt;p>Hey! You might notice something new down at the bottom of my blog posts. It&amp;rsquo;s a
comments section! You can leave comments on my ramblings if you have a Github
account and you sign in to it.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I&amp;rsquo;m using a system called &lt;a href="https://giscus.app/">giscus&lt;/a> for my comments. It means I
don&amp;rsquo;t have to worry about self-hosting anything, and I can just use github!
Specifically, Github discussions, which is a way for people to talk about a
repo on the site, and it means that I don&amp;rsquo;t need to handle anyone&amp;rsquo;s data
myself! If you don&amp;rsquo;t have a Github account, I highly encourage you to make one!
It&amp;rsquo;s a great community of people who make all sorts of cool open-source stuff,
and it&amp;rsquo;s free and secure enough that I use it to run my comments! If nothing
else, the ability to tell me why the comments section is a bad idea is a good
reason to sign up for Github and comment on this blog!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Game Engines [ARCHIVE]</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2021/07/12/game-engines-archive/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 10:01:29 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2021/07/12/game-engines-archive/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;strong>PLEASE NOTE: this is an archive from my original blog. It was my only post.&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;div class="highlight">&lt;pre tabindex="0" style="color:#fff;background-color:#111;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;">&lt;code class="language-txt" data-lang="txt">&lt;span style="display:flex;">&lt;span>Before we begin: A game engine is a tool which is used to create games. It
&lt;/span>&lt;/span>&lt;span style="display:flex;">&lt;span>usually has a user interface and a scripting language (a specialized programming
&lt;/span>&lt;/span>&lt;span style="display:flex;">&lt;span>language unique to the engine) of some sort.
&lt;/span>&lt;/span>&lt;span style="display:flex;">&lt;span>A game _framework_ is a library of code which can be added to your code so it&amp;#39;s
&lt;/span>&lt;/span>&lt;span style="display:flex;">&lt;span>easier to make a game. These generally require substantially more knowledge and
&lt;/span>&lt;/span>&lt;span style="display:flex;">&lt;span>coding skill.
&lt;/span>&lt;/span>&lt;/code>&lt;/pre>&lt;/div>&lt;p>So, as many of you know, &lt;a href="https://intangiblematter.itch.io">I like to make games.&lt;/a>
A lot. I&amp;rsquo;ve published four games (as
of writing) and have created several more. However, my choice of game engine
hasn&amp;rsquo;t always been consistent. The first engine I tried to use was, as is many
people&amp;rsquo;s first choice, Unity. My time with this engine was short, and I had a
great deal of trouble trying to grock how it works.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>