<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>General on IntangibleMatter</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/tags/general/</link><description>Recent content in General on IntangibleMatter</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 03:48:44 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://intangiblematter.github.io/tags/general/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Who Cares If I End Up on the No-Fly List</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2024/05/01/who-cares-if-i-end-up-on-the-no-fly-list/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 01:16:25 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2024/05/01/who-cares-if-i-end-up-on-the-no-fly-list/</guid><description>Jesus Christ. Jesus FUCKING Christ.
The fact that this alt-right bullshit has made it to mainstream Canadian politics is fucking terrifying.
I&amp;rsquo;ve had an idea for a game kicking around in my head for a while now, something commenting on the political situation in the world right now, specifically when it comes to transphobia.
Basic pitch is a stealth movement shooter where you assassinate prominent anti-catgirl figures. Catgirls are definitely not acting as a stand in for anything here, and you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t look into it further.</description></item><item><title>Fascism Litmus Test</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2024/03/19/fascism-litmus-test/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 10:31:29 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2024/03/19/fascism-litmus-test/</guid><description>As of writing, it has been 164 days since October 7th. In this time, we&amp;rsquo;ve seen an alarming rise in antisemitism, an open genocide&amp;hellip;
And an upsetting amount of people displaying how easy it is to sympathize with fascism.
As long as I&amp;rsquo;ve been politically aware, Israel has been&amp;hellip; a complicated topic. On the one hand, yes there&amp;rsquo;s a lot of antisemitism in the world even today, and it&amp;rsquo;s good to have a country where people can go that&amp;rsquo;s made so that they don&amp;rsquo;t have to worry about it.</description></item><item><title>How to Make a Screenspace Visualshader in Godot</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2024/01/25/how-to-make-a-screenspace-visualshader-in-godot/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 11:10:12 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2024/01/25/how-to-make-a-screenspace-visualshader-in-godot/</guid><description>Click here to skip to the instructions.
So Godot Engine has a really cool shader system, allowing you to do stuff like change the way lighting works in both 2D and 3D using nothing but shaders, and it additionally has a powerful VisualShader system. VisualShaders, for those who don&amp;rsquo;t know, are shaders that use a Shader Graph system instead of pure code. I&amp;rsquo;m not huge on node-based programming systems, so I usually elect to (poorly) write a shader myself, but I&amp;rsquo;m working on a game jam with a larger team than I ever have before right now, and they wanted to use the ShaderV addon because of how many cool things it has.</description></item><item><title>Installing Fmod Studio on Pop!_OS</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/08/03/installing-fmod-studio-on-pop_os/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 01:27:58 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/08/03/installing-fmod-studio-on-pop_os/</guid><description>So, as a game developer, I love FMOD. Advanced sound is always so cool to me! However, when installing FMOD Studio on Pop!_OS, you&amp;rsquo;ll run into an issue.
$ dpkg -i fmodstudio&amp;lt;version&amp;gt;.deb Package pulseaudio is not installed So, even though it requires a bit of editing files that you probably shouldn&amp;rsquo;t, it&amp;rsquo;s actually quite easy!
First, run dpkg -i --force-all fmodstudio&amp;lt;version&amp;gt;.deb. This installs FMOD Studio, and FMOD Studio will run just fine!</description></item><item><title>The Perfect Mac and Cheese (According to My Dead Dad)</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/05/27/the-perfect-mac-and-cheese-according-to-my-dead-dad/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 22:35:26 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/05/27/the-perfect-mac-and-cheese-according-to-my-dead-dad/</guid><description>My dad (or as I and my family called him, Lala,) had a lot of experience with making mac and cheese from a box. While he had cancer, he ate a lot of mac and cheese because most foods didn&amp;rsquo;t taste good to him because of all the stuff in his body to fight the cancer. One day, when he was too tired to make it himself, he told me how he always makes it.</description></item><item><title>Footpedal: A FOSS Audio Engine for Games</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/05/12/footpedal-a-foss-audio-engine-for-games/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 10:01:10 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/05/12/footpedal-a-foss-audio-engine-for-games/</guid><description>I love dynamic audio in games. Being a game developer, I want to add it to my own projects. Unfortunately, I&amp;rsquo;m broke and all existing solutions are expensive to use (at least without a giant splash screen when you boot up the game.) Obviously, being a programmer myself, I decided I&amp;rsquo;d try to write an audio engine on my own. This is, of course, a completely giant task, and I am not amazing at programming complex systems, especially at lower levels, so I pretty much gave up.</description></item><item><title>I'm Fine: a Short Film</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/05/05/im-fine-a-short-film/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 00:10:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/05/05/im-fine-a-short-film/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m Fine is a short film that I wrote, recorded, and filmed almost entirely by myself in late April of 2023 for my high school&amp;rsquo;s film fest. I&amp;rsquo;ve had ideas for various projects about my mental health for a few years now. This is the first project of this vein that I&amp;rsquo;ve completed, and it almost definitely won&amp;rsquo;t be the last. This film features me and three representations of various aspects of my mental health while anxiety screams over me, depression mopes while resting its head on the heater, and my own expectations of myself frantically justify why they exist by the mirror.</description></item><item><title>Comments</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/04/17/comments/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 15:58:35 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/04/17/comments/</guid><description>Hey! You might notice something new down at the bottom of my blog posts. It&amp;rsquo;s a comments section! You can leave comments on my ramblings if you have a Github account and you sign in to it.
I&amp;rsquo;m using a system called giscus for my comments. It means I don&amp;rsquo;t have to worry about self-hosting anything, and I can just use github! Specifically, Github discussions, which is a way for people to talk about a repo on the site, and it means that I don&amp;rsquo;t need to handle anyone&amp;rsquo;s data myself!</description></item><item><title>Game Engines [ARCHIVE]</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2021/07/12/game-engines-archive/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 10:01:29 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2021/07/12/game-engines-archive/</guid><description>PLEASE NOTE: this is an archive from my original blog. It was my only post.
Before we begin: A game engine is a tool which is used to create games. It usually has a user interface and a scripting language (a specialized programming language unique to the engine) of some sort. A game _framework_ is a library of code which can be added to your code so it&amp;#39;s easier to make a game.</description></item></channel></rss>