<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hantiplad on IntangibleMatter</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/hantiplad/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hantiplad on IntangibleMatter</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 09:25:27 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/hantiplad/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>You Can&#39;t Fight the Homestuck</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/10/30/you-cant-fight-the-homestuck/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 11:03:28 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/10/30/you-cant-fight-the-homestuck/</guid>
      <description>In August of this year I started reading one of the most infamous webcomics, parts of internet culture, and just general clusterfucks out there. Which is to say that I started reading Homestuck.&#xA;Homestuck, for those who don&amp;rsquo;t know, is/was a webcomic about four kids who play a game that results in the end of the world, and their efforts to create a new one. That&amp;rsquo;s the short version of it, and it also mentions nothing of the numerous flashes, incredible music, odd spin-offs and sidequests, its nature as a borderline cult, much to the distress of the creator, and all of the other chaos.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wallsocket</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/09/26/wallsocket/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 08:56:10 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/09/26/wallsocket/</guid>
      <description>Wallsocket, the new album released by underscores on September 22nd, 2023, has quickly and easily risen to be my album of the year. After a lead up of a variety of singles being released, almost all of which I greatly enjoyed, the album released with a great variety of genres, tones, themes, and characters, all while feeling like a very cohesive work.&#xA;Cops and Robbers pass&#xA;Locals (Girls like us) pass</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hangar</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/06/12/hangar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 11:20:26 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/06/12/hangar/</guid>
      <description>If you held me against a wall with a gun to my head asking me what my favourite song was, I&amp;rsquo;d probably have a fatal panic attack.&#xA;If I somehow managed to respond, however, I would probably say with very little hesitation that the answer is Hangar by 8485. It&amp;rsquo;s a song that means a lot to me, and that I&amp;rsquo;ve listened to more times than any other song in my music library.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s the New Wave of the Future!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/06/10/its-the-new-wave-of-the-future/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 08:25:02 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/06/10/its-the-new-wave-of-the-future/</guid>
      <description>My music taste changes constantly. I had a long time where I mostly listened to video game music, then a good few months where I mostly listened to electro. (Thanks, Just Shapes and Beats!) Recently, though, I&amp;rsquo;ve been listening to hyperpop. For those of you who don&amp;rsquo;t know, hyperpop is a musical genre which can be loosely defined as a type of music that borrows strongly from pop for its layout, early 2000s internet for its musical aesthetics, and pretty much whatever the hell the artist feels like for the lyrics.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Katana ZERO Is a Masterpiece</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/05/15/katana-zero-is-a-masterpiece/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 13:05:35 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/05/15/katana-zero-is-a-masterpiece/</guid>
      <description>Katana ZERO, for those of you who don&amp;rsquo;t know, is a 2019 video game created by Justin Standard (aka Askiisoft) and a few others. It features difficult side-scrolling action, tight combat, an amazing soundtrack, beautiful pixel art, and one of my favourite stories of the past decade. While I could rave about it for hours, I&amp;rsquo;ll do my best to keep this article finite.&#xA;Also, in case it wasn&amp;rsquo;t obvious, there will be MAJOR SPOILERS for Katana ZERO!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Owl House Was Special</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/04/08/the-owl-house-was-special/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 16:38:12 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/04/08/the-owl-house-was-special/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m writing this article as I&amp;rsquo;m finishing The Owl House series finale, something I&amp;rsquo;ve been waiting for for a few years now.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
