<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Short on IntangibleMatter</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/short/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Short on IntangibleMatter</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 09:25:27 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/short/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Impostor Syndrome, Adhd, and Burgers</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/05/31/impostor-syndrome-adhd-and-burgers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 12:24:11 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/05/31/impostor-syndrome-adhd-and-burgers/</guid>
      <description>So this is just a short little update. At the time of writing this, I&amp;rsquo;m currently waiting for a burger because I have nothing better to do in the time between now and when I go and talk to a whole bunch of mental health people to find out if my mental illness is disruptive enough to the system to give me support for something that I&amp;rsquo;ve recently realized has been making my whole life harder than it has to be.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eggs Like Russian Dolls</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/05/23/eggs-like-russian-dolls/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 15:28:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/05/23/eggs-like-russian-dolls/</guid>
      <description>So a while back I made a post about how my egg had cracked, and that I was, disappointingly, cis.&#xA;In retrospect, I now think that the egg had just cracked to reveal another egg. I just kind of default to being cis because it&amp;rsquo;s what i know, and because I feel uncomfortable with uncertainty, especially about core parts of myself. I don&amp;rsquo;t think any truly cis person could say the phrase &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m cis in the way that I&amp;rsquo;d do lines of estrogen&amp;rdquo; with a straight face.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You&#39;ve Cracked Your Egg, Now Fry in It</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/04/28/youve-cracked-your-egg-now-fry-in-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 00:45:36 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/04/28/youve-cracked-your-egg-now-fry-in-it/</guid>
      <description>A while back I made a post about my gender and my experience in questioning. I&amp;rsquo;m happy to announce that my egg has recently cracked! And&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;m not trans.&#xA;Disappointing, right? I know, I was disappointed too. But it&amp;rsquo;s fine to not be a member of a group with so many cool members oh my god it&amp;rsquo;s statistically anomalous how many cool trans people there are. What I am, however, is someone who doesn&amp;rsquo;t strongly identify with the societal construct of masculinity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>That One Person Who Presses All the Buttons</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/04/26/that-one-person-who-presses-all-the-buttons/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 19:12:24 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/04/26/that-one-person-who-presses-all-the-buttons/</guid>
      <description>Do you have that one person who just somehow perfectly presses the buttons on all of your insecurities without even knowing it? That person who just seems so untouchable and perfect that their mere existence seems like some cosmic joke at your expense? Even if you know they&amp;rsquo;re still human, and that they also deal with issues like humans do, it just feels like they&amp;rsquo;ve figured out a method for hiding all of their struggles perfectly?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mirrors</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/02/23/mirrors/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 13:59:16 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/02/23/mirrors/</guid>
      <description>I feel like the people we get along best with are always, to some degree, mirrors of ourselves. My closest friends all mirror some aspect of myself, and I some aspect of them. The more you mirror, the more likely you are to be friends.&#xA;A lot of my friends don&amp;rsquo;t have much in common, aside from being generally smart in various ways, and always having something or another that they can talk your ear off about.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
