<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on IntangibleMatter</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on IntangibleMatter</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 00:45:36 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>You've Cracked Your Egg, Now Fry in It</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/04/28/youve-cracked-your-egg-now-fry-in-it/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 00:45:36 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/04/28/youve-cracked-your-egg-now-fry-in-it/</guid><description>A while back I made a post about my gender and my experience in questioning. I&amp;rsquo;m happy to announce that my egg has recently cracked! And&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;m not trans.
Disappointing, right? I know, I was disappointed too. But it&amp;rsquo;s fine to not be a member of a group with so many cool members oh my god it&amp;rsquo;s statistically anomalous how many cool trans people there are. What I am, however, is someone who doesn&amp;rsquo;t strongly identify with the societal construct of masculinity.</description></item><item><title>That One Person Who Presses All the Buttons</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/04/26/that-one-person-who-presses-all-the-buttons/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 19:12:24 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/04/26/that-one-person-who-presses-all-the-buttons/</guid><description>Do you have that one person who just somehow perfectly presses the buttons on all of your insecurities without even knowing it? That person who just seems so untouchable and perfect that their mere existence seems like some cosmic joke at your expense? Even if you know they&amp;rsquo;re still human, and that they also deal with issues like humans do, it just feels like they&amp;rsquo;ve figured out a method for hiding all of their struggles perfectly?</description></item><item><title>Comments</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/04/17/comments/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 15:58:35 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/04/17/comments/</guid><description>Hey! You might notice something new down at the bottom of my blog posts. It&amp;rsquo;s a comments section! You can leave comments on my ramblings if you have a Github account and you sign in to it.
I&amp;rsquo;m using a system called giscus for my comments. It means I don&amp;rsquo;t have to worry about self-hosting anything, and I can just use github! Specifically, Github discussions, which is a way for people to talk about a repo on the site, and it means that I don&amp;rsquo;t need to handle anyone&amp;rsquo;s data myself!</description></item><item><title>Eggs and Gender</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/03/28/eggs-and-gender/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 09:10:26 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/03/28/eggs-and-gender/</guid><description>Gender is weird.
It&amp;rsquo;s such a social construct yet our society has been built on it on such a fundamental level that to most it&amp;rsquo;s a huge deal for most people to even consider changing from the gender they&amp;rsquo;ve been assigned. It&amp;rsquo;s an even bigger deal because of all the genocidal language that&amp;rsquo;s getting thrown around by neofascists about trans people as of late.
Which, of course, means it&amp;rsquo;s a great time to resume the questioning I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing on and off for the last 5 years!</description></item><item><title>A Brief Hantiplad About Everything Everywhere All At Once</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/03/22/a-brief-hantiplad-about-everything-everywhere-all-at-once/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 00:51:09 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/03/22/a-brief-hantiplad-about-everything-everywhere-all-at-once/</guid><description>So I finally got to watch that movie everyone was talking about last year. It&amp;rsquo;s honestly even better than everyone says. The effects were amazing, the writing was fantastic, and the actors were all&amp;hellip; *chef&amp;rsquo;s kiss*.
Our deadpan-hyper chaotic-evil queen.
My favourite character was easily Jobu Tupekai. She&amp;rsquo;s honestly everything I aspire to be. A cool, nihilistic, reality warping, amazing looking young adult who created an object that can destroy the most powerful people somewhat out of boredom.</description></item><item><title>Mirrors</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/02/23/mirrors/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 13:59:16 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/02/23/mirrors/</guid><description>I feel like the people we get along best with are always, to some degree, mirrors of ourselves. My closest friends all mirror some aspect of myself, and I some aspect of them. The more you mirror, the more likely you are to be friends.
A lot of my friends don&amp;rsquo;t have much in common, aside from being generally smart in various ways, and always having something or another that they can talk your ear off about.</description></item><item><title>Game Engines [ARCHIVE]</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2021/07/12/game-engines-archive/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 10:01:29 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2021/07/12/game-engines-archive/</guid><description>PLEASE NOTE: this is an archive from my original blog. It was my only post.
Before we begin: A game engine is a tool which is used to create games. It usually has a user interface and a scripting language (a specialized programming language unique to the engine) of some sort. A game _framework_ is a library of code which can be added to your code so it&amp;#39;s easier to make a game.</description></item></channel></rss>