<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on IntangibleMatter</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on IntangibleMatter</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 00:10:38 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Rare Moments You Feel Like You're Real</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/06/08/the-rare-moments-you-feel-like-youre-real/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 00:10:38 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/06/08/the-rare-moments-you-feel-like-youre-real/</guid><description>Here&amp;#39;s a song that I like. Might be good to listen to with this post. Idk.
You know how some people feel like they&amp;rsquo;re the only real person in the world?
I have the opposite problem.
To some degree.:w
Society paints a very strong picture in our minds of what a &amp;ldquo;teenager&amp;rdquo; is supposed to do. And I very rarely find myself meeting those expectations. Whether it&amp;rsquo;s because of my anxiety, depression, or just general tendencies to isolate myself socially (lockdown was a bit of a dream come true), I tend to find myself working on my computer, browsing the internet, and just being alone with my (admittedly distressing) thoughts.</description></item><item><title>My First Fullindie Meetup</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/06/06/my-first-fullindie-meetup/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 23:27:46 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/06/06/my-first-fullindie-meetup/</guid><description>So&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;m writing this on the ferry ride home from my very first FullIndie meetup! I basically got on a bus right after school to get down to the ferry, then I went into Vancouer and&amp;hellip; ate food?
Also all of this was with my friend River. They&amp;rsquo;re cool. Check them out. Without whom I probably would&amp;rsquo;ve been having an anxiety attack for the whole trip so&amp;hellip; thanks, Riv!
After we ate, we went down to the Skytrain and went down to the place where the meetup was happening.</description></item><item><title>Impostor Syndrome, Adhd, and Burgers</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/05/31/impostor-syndrome-adhd-and-burgers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 12:24:11 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/05/31/impostor-syndrome-adhd-and-burgers/</guid><description>So this is just a short little update. At the time of writing this, I&amp;rsquo;m currently waiting for a burger because I have nothing better to do in the time between now and when I go and talk to a whole bunch of mental health people to find out if my mental illness is disruptive enough to the system to give me support for something that I&amp;rsquo;ve recently realized has been making my whole life harder than it has to be.</description></item><item><title>The Perfect Mac and Cheese (According to My Dead Dad)</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/05/27/the-perfect-mac-and-cheese-according-to-my-dead-dad/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 22:35:26 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/05/27/the-perfect-mac-and-cheese-according-to-my-dead-dad/</guid><description>My dad (or as I and my family called him, Lala,) had a lot of experience with making mac and cheese from a box. While he had cancer, he ate a lot of mac and cheese because most foods didn&amp;rsquo;t taste good to him because of all the stuff in his body to fight the cancer. One day, when he was too tired to make it himself, he told me how he always makes it.</description></item><item><title>Eggs Like Russian Dolls</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/05/23/eggs-like-russian-dolls/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 15:28:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/05/23/eggs-like-russian-dolls/</guid><description>So a while back I made a post about how my egg had cracked, and that I was, disappointingly, cis.
In retrospect, I now think that the egg had just cracked to reveal another egg. I just kind of default to being cis because it&amp;rsquo;s what i know, and because I feel uncomfortable with uncertainty, especially about core parts of myself. I don&amp;rsquo;t think any truly cis person could say the phrase &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m cis in the way that I&amp;rsquo;d do lines of estrogen&amp;rdquo; with a straight face.</description></item><item><title>Oops! All Parasocial!</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/05/23/oops-all-parasocial/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 10:50:45 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/05/23/oops-all-parasocial/</guid><description>So&amp;hellip; it&amp;rsquo;s not exactly a secret that I&amp;rsquo;ve struggled to make friendships in life. I&amp;rsquo;ve never been good at reading social signals, I&amp;rsquo;m always direct about things that most people are at least somewhat awkward about, and I&amp;rsquo;ve always had a lot of niche intrests that most people I know knew little to nothing about. On top of that, I have social anxiety! Which for me means that obviously someone not replying for a while means that I made a social misstep that I didn&amp;rsquo;t notice and not that they&amp;rsquo;re busy or something.</description></item><item><title>The Heat Is Horrible</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/05/15/the-heat-is-horrible/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 08:25:40 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/05/15/the-heat-is-horrible/</guid><description>So&amp;hellip; it&amp;rsquo;s mid May and the temperature has suddenly shot up by about 10 degrees where I live. If you lived in Ontario or something, this would probably be normal, but I live in southwest BC. The temperature getting above or below 8-12 degrees is weird, especially this suddenly. Or I guess it isn&amp;rsquo;t weird, just miserable. Another sucky part of it is that my town isn&amp;rsquo;t frequently this hot so most buildings don&amp;rsquo;t have air conditioning.</description></item><item><title>Footpedal: A FOSS Audio Engine for Games</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/05/12/footpedal-a-foss-audio-engine-for-games/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 10:01:10 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/05/12/footpedal-a-foss-audio-engine-for-games/</guid><description>I love dynamic audio in games. Being a game developer, I want to add it to my own projects. Unfortunately, I&amp;rsquo;m broke and all existing solutions are expensive to use (at least without a giant splash screen when you boot up the game.) Obviously, being a programmer myself, I decided I&amp;rsquo;d try to write an audio engine on my own. This is, of course, a completely giant task, and I am not amazing at programming complex systems, especially at lower levels, so I pretty much gave up.</description></item><item><title>I'm Fine: a Short Film</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/05/05/im-fine-a-short-film/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 00:10:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/05/05/im-fine-a-short-film/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m Fine is a short film that I wrote, recorded, and filmed almost entirely by myself in late April of 2023 for my high school&amp;rsquo;s film fest. I&amp;rsquo;ve had ideas for various projects about my mental health for a few years now. This is the first project of this vein that I&amp;rsquo;ve completed, and it almost definitely won&amp;rsquo;t be the last. This film features me and three representations of various aspects of my mental health while anxiety screams over me, depression mopes while resting its head on the heater, and my own expectations of myself frantically justify why they exist by the mirror.</description></item><item><title>You've Cracked Your Egg, Now Fry in It</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/04/28/youve-cracked-your-egg-now-fry-in-it/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 00:45:36 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/04/28/youve-cracked-your-egg-now-fry-in-it/</guid><description>A while back I made a post about my gender and my experience in questioning. I&amp;rsquo;m happy to announce that my egg has recently cracked! And&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;m not trans.
Disappointing, right? I know, I was disappointed too. But it&amp;rsquo;s fine to not be a member of a group with so many cool members oh my god it&amp;rsquo;s statistically anomalous how many cool trans people there are. What I am, however, is someone who doesn&amp;rsquo;t strongly identify with the societal construct of masculinity.</description></item><item><title>That One Person Who Presses All the Buttons</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/04/26/that-one-person-who-presses-all-the-buttons/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 19:12:24 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/04/26/that-one-person-who-presses-all-the-buttons/</guid><description>Do you have that one person who just somehow perfectly presses the buttons on all of your insecurities without even knowing it? That person who just seems so untouchable and perfect that their mere existence seems like some cosmic joke at your expense? Even if you know they&amp;rsquo;re still human, and that they also deal with issues like humans do, it just feels like they&amp;rsquo;ve figured out a method for hiding all of their struggles perfectly?</description></item><item><title>Comments</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/04/17/comments/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 15:58:35 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/04/17/comments/</guid><description>Hey! You might notice something new down at the bottom of my blog posts. It&amp;rsquo;s a comments section! You can leave comments on my ramblings if you have a Github account and you sign in to it.
I&amp;rsquo;m using a system called giscus for my comments. It means I don&amp;rsquo;t have to worry about self-hosting anything, and I can just use github! Specifically, Github discussions, which is a way for people to talk about a repo on the site, and it means that I don&amp;rsquo;t need to handle anyone&amp;rsquo;s data myself!</description></item><item><title>Eggs and Gender</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/03/28/eggs-and-gender/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 09:10:26 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/03/28/eggs-and-gender/</guid><description>Gender is weird.
It&amp;rsquo;s such a social construct yet our society has been built on it on such a fundamental level that to most it&amp;rsquo;s a huge deal for most people to even consider changing from the gender they&amp;rsquo;ve been assigned. It&amp;rsquo;s an even bigger deal because of all the genocidal language that&amp;rsquo;s getting thrown around by neofascists about trans people as of late.
Which, of course, means it&amp;rsquo;s a great time to resume the questioning I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing on and off for the last 5 years!</description></item><item><title>A Brief Hantiplad About Everything Everywhere All At Once</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/03/22/a-brief-hantiplad-about-everything-everywhere-all-at-once/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 00:51:09 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/03/22/a-brief-hantiplad-about-everything-everywhere-all-at-once/</guid><description>So I finally got to watch that movie everyone was talking about last year. It&amp;rsquo;s honestly even better than everyone says. The effects were amazing, the writing was fantastic, and the actors were all&amp;hellip; *chef&amp;rsquo;s kiss*.
Our deadpan-hyper chaotic-evil queen.
My favourite character was easily Jobu Tupekai. She&amp;rsquo;s honestly everything I aspire to be. A cool, nihilistic, reality warping, amazing looking young adult who created an object that can destroy the most powerful people somewhat out of boredom.</description></item><item><title>Mirrors</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/02/23/mirrors/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 13:59:16 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/02/23/mirrors/</guid><description>I feel like the people we get along best with are always, to some degree, mirrors of ourselves. My closest friends all mirror some aspect of myself, and I some aspect of them. The more you mirror, the more likely you are to be friends.
A lot of my friends don&amp;rsquo;t have much in common, aside from being generally smart in various ways, and always having something or another that they can talk your ear off about.</description></item><item><title>Game Engines [ARCHIVE]</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2021/07/12/game-engines-archive/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 10:01:29 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2021/07/12/game-engines-archive/</guid><description>PLEASE NOTE: this is an archive from my original blog. It was my only post.
Before we begin: A game engine is a tool which is used to create games. It usually has a user interface and a scripting language (a specialized programming language unique to the engine) of some sort. A game _framework_ is a library of code which can be added to your code so it&amp;#39;s easier to make a game.</description></item></channel></rss>