<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Projects on IntangibleMatter</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/tags/projects/</link><description>Recent content in Projects on IntangibleMatter</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 09:25:27 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://intangiblematter.github.io/tags/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Footpedal: A FOSS Audio Engine for Games</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/05/12/footpedal-a-foss-audio-engine-for-games/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 10:01:10 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/05/12/footpedal-a-foss-audio-engine-for-games/</guid><description>I love dynamic audio in games. Being a game developer, I want to add it to my own projects. Unfortunately, I&amp;rsquo;m broke and all existing solutions are expensive to use (at least without a giant splash screen when you boot up the game.) Obviously, being a programmer myself, I decided I&amp;rsquo;d try to write an audio engine on my own. This is, of course, a completely giant task, and I am not amazing at programming complex systems, especially at lower levels, so I pretty much gave up.</description></item><item><title>I'm Fine: a Short Film</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/05/05/im-fine-a-short-film/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 00:10:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/05/05/im-fine-a-short-film/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m Fine is a short film that I wrote, recorded, and filmed almost entirely by myself in late April of 2023 for my high school&amp;rsquo;s film fest. I&amp;rsquo;ve had ideas for various projects about my mental health for a few years now. This is the first project of this vein that I&amp;rsquo;ve completed, and it almost definitely won&amp;rsquo;t be the last. This film features me and three representations of various aspects of my mental health while anxiety screams over me, depression mopes while resting its head on the heater, and my own expectations of myself frantically justify why they exist by the mirror.</description></item></channel></rss>