<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>media on IntangibleMatter</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/tags/media/</link><description>Recent content in media on IntangibleMatter</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 00:01:00 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://intangiblematter.github.io/tags/media/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Don Hertzfeldt, Hangar, and the Desire to Be Human</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/07/16/don-hertzfeldt-hangar-and-the-desire-to-be-human/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 00:01:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/07/16/don-hertzfeldt-hangar-and-the-desire-to-be-human/</guid><description>So if you&amp;rsquo;ve spent any amount of time talking to me (or, more accurately, listening to me talk,) you&amp;rsquo;ve probably heard me talk about Don Hertzfeldt. Don Hertzfeldt is a self-described Oscar-losing filmmaker. He makes animated films starring stick figures, dry narration, and some of the most beautiful stories I&amp;rsquo;ve ever seen. His debut feature, It&amp;rsquo;s Such A Beautiful Day, is an hour-long attack on the senses, featuring filmmaking techniques taken to their limits.</description></item><item><title>I'm Fine: a Short Film</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/05/05/im-fine-a-short-film/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 00:10:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/05/05/im-fine-a-short-film/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m Fine is a short film that I wrote, recorded, and filmed almost entirely by myself in late April of 2023 for my high school&amp;rsquo;s film fest. I&amp;rsquo;ve had ideas for various projects about my mental health for a few years now. This is the first project of this vein that I&amp;rsquo;ve completed, and it almost definitely won&amp;rsquo;t be the last. This film features me and three representations of various aspects of my mental health while anxiety screams over me, depression mopes while resting its head on the heater, and my own expectations of myself frantically justify why they exist by the mirror.</description></item><item><title>A Brief Hantiplad About Everything Everywhere All At Once</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/03/22/a-brief-hantiplad-about-everything-everywhere-all-at-once/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 00:51:09 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/03/22/a-brief-hantiplad-about-everything-everywhere-all-at-once/</guid><description>So I finally got to watch that movie everyone was talking about last year. It&amp;rsquo;s honestly even better than everyone says. The effects were amazing, the writing was fantastic, and the actors were all&amp;hellip; *chef&amp;rsquo;s kiss*.
Our deadpan-hyper chaotic-evil queen.
My favourite character was easily Jobu Tupekai. She&amp;rsquo;s honestly everything I aspire to be. A cool, nihilistic, reality warping, amazing looking young adult who created an object that can destroy the most powerful people somewhat out of boredom.</description></item></channel></rss>