<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>gamedev on IntangibleMatter</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/tags/gamedev/</link><description>Recent content in gamedev on IntangibleMatter</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 23:27:46 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://intangiblematter.github.io/tags/gamedev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>My First Fullindie Meetup</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/personal/2023/06/06/my-first-fullindie-meetup/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 23:27:46 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/personal/2023/06/06/my-first-fullindie-meetup/</guid><description>So&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;m writing this on the ferry ride home from my very first FullIndie meetup! I basically got on a bus right after school to get down to the ferry, then I went into Vancouer and&amp;hellip; ate food?
Also all of this was with my friend River. They&amp;rsquo;re cool. Check them out. Without whom I probably would&amp;rsquo;ve been having an anxiety attack for the whole trip so&amp;hellip; thanks, Riv!
After we ate, we went down to the Skytrain and went down to the place where the meetup was happening.</description></item><item><title>Footpedal: A FOSS Audio Engine for Games</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/05/12/footpedal-a-foss-audio-engine-for-games/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 10:01:10 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/05/12/footpedal-a-foss-audio-engine-for-games/</guid><description>I love dynamic audio in games. Being a game developer, I want to add it to my own projects. Unfortunately, I&amp;rsquo;m broke and all existing solutions are expensive to use (at least without a giant splash screen when you boot up the game.) Obviously, being a programmer myself, I decided I&amp;rsquo;d try to write an audio engine on my own. This is, of course, a completely giant task, and I am not amazing at programming complex systems, especially at lower levels, so I pretty much gave up.</description></item><item><title>Game Engines [ARCHIVE]</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2021/07/12/game-engines-archive/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 10:01:29 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2021/07/12/game-engines-archive/</guid><description>PLEASE NOTE: this is an archive from my original blog. It was my only post.
Before we begin: A game engine is a tool which is used to create games. It usually has a user interface and a scripting language (a specialized programming language unique to the engine) of some sort. A game _framework_ is a library of code which can be added to your code so it&amp;#39;s easier to make a game.</description></item></channel></rss>