<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Eggs on IntangibleMatter</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/tags/eggs/</link><description>Recent content in Eggs on IntangibleMatter</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 05:24:41 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://intangiblematter.github.io/tags/eggs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>YAUFYAITG</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2024/04/20/yaufyaitg/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 17:33:03 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2024/04/20/yaufyaitg/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re wondering what the title stands for, it&amp;rsquo;s Yet Another Update From Yet Another Internet Trans Girl, and this post is exactly what it says on the tin.
I have some posts about my previous gender questioning on this page, so it&amp;rsquo;s not anything new. But tl;dr for anyone who hasn&amp;rsquo;t read the previous posts: I&amp;rsquo;m gender questioning, fit a lot of tropes for transfems, spend a ton of time thinking about what it would be like to be a girl, wishing I was a girl, knowing that girls (especially trans ones) have a lot harder time moving through life than cis guys do, but still feeling like it would be easier, etc, etc, etc.</description></item><item><title>Eggs Like Russian Dolls</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/05/23/eggs-like-russian-dolls/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 15:28:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/05/23/eggs-like-russian-dolls/</guid><description>So a while back I made a post about how my egg had cracked, and that I was, disappointingly, cis.
In retrospect, I now think that the egg had just cracked to reveal another egg. I just kind of default to being cis because it&amp;rsquo;s what i know, and because I feel uncomfortable with uncertainty, especially about core parts of myself. I don&amp;rsquo;t think any truly cis person could say the phrase &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m cis in the way that I&amp;rsquo;d do lines of estrogen&amp;rdquo; with a straight face.</description></item><item><title>You've Cracked Your Egg, Now Fry in It</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/04/28/youve-cracked-your-egg-now-fry-in-it/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 00:45:36 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/04/28/youve-cracked-your-egg-now-fry-in-it/</guid><description>A while back I made a post about my gender and my experience in questioning. I&amp;rsquo;m happy to announce that my egg has recently cracked! And&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;m not trans.
Disappointing, right? I know, I was disappointed too. But it&amp;rsquo;s fine to not be a member of a group with so many cool members oh my god it&amp;rsquo;s statistically anomalous how many cool trans people there are. What I am, however, is someone who doesn&amp;rsquo;t strongly identify with the societal construct of masculinity.</description></item><item><title>Eggs and Gender</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/03/28/eggs-and-gender/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 09:10:26 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/posts/2023/03/28/eggs-and-gender/</guid><description>Gender is weird.
It&amp;rsquo;s such a social construct yet our society has been built on it on such a fundamental level that to most it&amp;rsquo;s a huge deal for most people to even consider changing from the gender they&amp;rsquo;ve been assigned. It&amp;rsquo;s an even bigger deal because of all the genocidal language that&amp;rsquo;s getting thrown around by neofascists about trans people as of late.
Which, of course, means it&amp;rsquo;s a great time to resume the questioning I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing on and off for the last 5 years!</description></item></channel></rss>