<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tutorial on IntangibleMatter</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/tutorial/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tutorial on IntangibleMatter</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 09:25:27 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/tutorial/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Make a Screenspace Visualshader in Godot</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2024/01/25/how-to-make-a-screenspace-visualshader-in-godot/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 11:10:12 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2024/01/25/how-to-make-a-screenspace-visualshader-in-godot/</guid>
      <description>Click here to skip to the instructions.&#xA;So Godot Engine has a really cool shader system, allowing you to do stuff like change the way lighting works in both 2D and 3D using nothing but shaders, and it additionally has a powerful VisualShader system. VisualShaders, for those who don&amp;rsquo;t know, are shaders that use a Shader Graph system instead of pure code. I&amp;rsquo;m not huge on node-based programming systems, so I usually elect to (poorly) write a shader myself, but I&amp;rsquo;m working on a game jam with a larger team than I ever have before right now, and they wanted to use the ShaderV addon because of how many cool things it has.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Beginner&#39;s Guide to File Management</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/11/15/the-beginners-guide-to-file-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 02:57:11 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/11/15/the-beginners-guide-to-file-management/</guid>
      <description>So, it has come to my attention as of late that most people my age and younger were never taught how to properly organize their files. As someone born in 2006, I grew up on Windows XP, so I was forced to learn how to organize files, or else my entire computer would be a mess. I got more training later through my life thanks to my dad&amp;rsquo;s (who I called &amp;lsquo;Lala&amp;rsquo;) excellent file organization, and the face that in order to be effective in game development you need an effective folder structure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Installing Fmod Studio on Pop!_OS</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/08/03/installing-fmod-studio-on-pop_os/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 01:27:58 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/08/03/installing-fmod-studio-on-pop_os/</guid>
      <description>So, as a game developer, I love FMOD. Advanced sound is always so cool to me! However, when installing FMOD Studio on Pop!_OS, you&amp;rsquo;ll run into an issue.&#xA;$ dpkg -i fmodstudio&amp;lt;version&amp;gt;.deb Package pulseaudio is not installed So, even though it requires a bit of editing files that you probably shouldn&amp;rsquo;t, it&amp;rsquo;s actually quite easy!&#xA;First, run dpkg -i --force-all fmodstudio&amp;lt;version&amp;gt;.deb. This installs FMOD Studio, and FMOD Studio will run just fine!</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
