<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>traumadump on IntangibleMatter</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/tags/traumadump/</link><description>Recent content in traumadump on IntangibleMatter</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 10:50:45 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://intangiblematter.github.io/tags/traumadump/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Oops! All Parasocial!</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/personal/2023/05/23/oops-all-parasocial/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 10:50:45 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/personal/2023/05/23/oops-all-parasocial/</guid><description>So&amp;hellip; it&amp;rsquo;s not exactly a secret that I&amp;rsquo;ve struggled to make friendships in life. I&amp;rsquo;ve never been good at reading social signals, I&amp;rsquo;m always direct about things that most people are at least somewhat awkward about, and I&amp;rsquo;ve always had a lot of niche intrests that most people I know knew little to nothing about. On top of that, I have social anxiety! Which for me means that obviously someone not replying for a while means that I made a social misstep that I didn&amp;rsquo;t notice and not that they&amp;rsquo;re busy or something.</description></item><item><title>I'm Fine: a Short Film</title><link>https://intangiblematter.github.io/personal/2023/05/05/im-fine-a-short-film/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 00:10:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://intangiblematter.github.io/personal/2023/05/05/im-fine-a-short-film/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m Fine is a short film that I wrote, recorded, and filmed almost entirely by myself in late April of 2023 for my high school&amp;rsquo;s film fest. I&amp;rsquo;ve had ideas for various projects about my mental health for a few years now. This is the first project of this vein that I&amp;rsquo;ve completed, and it almost definitely won&amp;rsquo;t be the last. This film features me and three representations of various aspects of my mental health while anxiety screams over me, depression mopes while resting its head on the heater, and my own expectations of myself frantically justify why they exist by the mirror.</description></item></channel></rss>