<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>General on IntangibleMatter</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/general/</link>
    <description>Recent content in General on IntangibleMatter</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 09:25:27 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/general/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Make a Screenspace Visualshader in Godot</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2024/01/25/how-to-make-a-screenspace-visualshader-in-godot/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 11:10:12 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2024/01/25/how-to-make-a-screenspace-visualshader-in-godot/</guid>
      <description>Click here to skip to the instructions.&#xA;So Godot Engine has a really cool shader system, allowing you to do stuff like change the way lighting works in both 2D and 3D using nothing but shaders, and it additionally has a powerful VisualShader system. VisualShaders, for those who don&amp;rsquo;t know, are shaders that use a Shader Graph system instead of pure code. I&amp;rsquo;m not huge on node-based programming systems, so I usually elect to (poorly) write a shader myself, but I&amp;rsquo;m working on a game jam with a larger team than I ever have before right now, and they wanted to use the ShaderV addon because of how many cool things it has.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECDL a New File Type for ECS Engines</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/12/23/ecdl-a-new-file-type-for-ecs-engines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 14:39:25 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/12/23/ecdl-a-new-file-type-for-ecs-engines/</guid>
      <description>ECDL, Or Entity Component Definition Language, is a new Markup Language (Technically two) designed for Defining Entities and Components in Entity Component Systems, but more specifically the new engine I&amp;rsquo;ve started work on both against my better judgment and the advice of friends. ECDL can be split into two different markup languages that write quite similarly. Let&amp;rsquo; start with what I consider the simpler of the two.&#xA;EDL - Entity Definition Language EDL, or Entity Definition Language, is used for, well, defining entities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECS vs OOP, or Why I Will Never be Happy With a Game Engine</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/12/18/ecs-vs-oop-or-why-i-will-never-be-happy-with-a-game-engine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 08:24:31 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/12/18/ecs-vs-oop-or-why-i-will-never-be-happy-with-a-game-engine/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carol Dontlookup and Media After Covid</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/12/17/carol-dontlookup-and-media-after-covid/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 02:20:36 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/12/17/carol-dontlookup-and-media-after-covid/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Beginner&#39;s Guide to File Management</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/11/15/the-beginners-guide-to-file-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 02:57:11 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/11/15/the-beginners-guide-to-file-management/</guid>
      <description>So, it has come to my attention as of late that most people my age and younger were never taught how to properly organize their files. As someone born in 2006, I grew up on Windows XP, so I was forced to learn how to organize files, or else my entire computer would be a mess. I got more training later through my life thanks to my dad&amp;rsquo;s (who I called &amp;lsquo;Lala&amp;rsquo;) excellent file organization, and the face that in order to be effective in game development you need an effective folder structure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plague Town</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/08/24/plague-town/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 05:13:25 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/08/24/plague-town/</guid>
      <description>Plague Town by 8485 is an incredibly special album to me.&#xA;While I started out listening to only one or two songs from it, over the next year it always had a song that was exactly what I needed when I needed it, and I slowly added all five songs on the EP to my rotation. From the longing, echoing synths of Hangar to the lying on the floor breakup song Southview, there was always something special in this album for me.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Installing Fmod Studio on Pop!_OS</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/08/03/installing-fmod-studio-on-pop_os/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 01:27:58 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/08/03/installing-fmod-studio-on-pop_os/</guid>
      <description>So, as a game developer, I love FMOD. Advanced sound is always so cool to me! However, when installing FMOD Studio on Pop!_OS, you&amp;rsquo;ll run into an issue.&#xA;$ dpkg -i fmodstudio&amp;lt;version&amp;gt;.deb Package pulseaudio is not installed So, even though it requires a bit of editing files that you probably shouldn&amp;rsquo;t, it&amp;rsquo;s actually quite easy!&#xA;First, run dpkg -i --force-all fmodstudio&amp;lt;version&amp;gt;.deb. This installs FMOD Studio, and FMOD Studio will run just fine!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Perfect Mac and Cheese (According to My Dead Dad)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/05/27/the-perfect-mac-and-cheese-according-to-my-dead-dad/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 22:35:26 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/05/27/the-perfect-mac-and-cheese-according-to-my-dead-dad/</guid>
      <description>My dad (or as I and my family called him, Lala,) had a lot of experience with making mac and cheese from a box. While he had cancer, he ate a lot of mac and cheese because most foods didn&amp;rsquo;t taste good to him because of all the stuff in his body to fight the cancer. One day, when he was too tired to make it himself, he told me how he always makes it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Footpedal: A FOSS Audio Engine for Games</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/05/12/footpedal-a-foss-audio-engine-for-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 10:01:10 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/05/12/footpedal-a-foss-audio-engine-for-games/</guid>
      <description>I love dynamic audio in games. Being a game developer, I want to add it to my own projects. Unfortunately, I&amp;rsquo;m broke and all existing solutions are expensive to use (at least without a giant splash screen when you boot up the game.) Obviously, being a programmer myself, I decided I&amp;rsquo;d try to write an audio engine on my own. This is, of course, a completely giant task, and I am not amazing at programming complex systems, especially at lower levels, so I pretty much gave up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m Fine: a Short Film</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/05/05/im-fine-a-short-film/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 00:10:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/05/05/im-fine-a-short-film/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m Fine is a short film that I wrote, recorded, and filmed almost entirely by myself in late April of 2023 for my high school&amp;rsquo;s film fest. I&amp;rsquo;ve had ideas for various projects about my mental health for a few years now. This is the first project of this vein that I&amp;rsquo;ve completed, and it almost definitely won&amp;rsquo;t be the last. This film features me and three representations of various aspects of my mental health while anxiety screams over me, depression mopes while resting its head on the heater, and my own expectations of myself frantically justify why they exist by the mirror.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comments</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/04/17/comments/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 15:58:35 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/04/17/comments/</guid>
      <description>Hey! You might notice something new down at the bottom of my blog posts. It&amp;rsquo;s a comments section! You can leave comments on my ramblings if you have a Github account and you sign in to it.&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;m using a system called giscus for my comments. It means I don&amp;rsquo;t have to worry about self-hosting anything, and I can just use github! Specifically, Github discussions, which is a way for people to talk about a repo on the site, and it means that I don&amp;rsquo;t need to handle anyone&amp;rsquo;s data myself!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don Hertzfeldt and the Meaning of Death</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/02/22/don-hertzfeldt-and-the-meaning-of-death/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 20:55:44 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/02/22/don-hertzfeldt-and-the-meaning-of-death/</guid>
      <description>Don Hertzfeldt, if you haven&amp;rsquo;t heard of him, is a filmmaker with a simple yet distinct art style. His works It&amp;rsquo;s Such a Beautiful Day and the World of Tomorrow series are some of the most</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test Post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/01/17/test-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 11:09:46 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/01/17/test-post/</guid>
      <description>This post is just here so my blog isn&amp;rsquo;t empty&#xA;Definitely deleting it soon.&#xA;Bye :)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Game Engines [ARCHIVE]</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2021/07/12/game-engines-archive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 10:01:29 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2021/07/12/game-engines-archive/</guid>
      <description>PLEASE NOTE: this is an archive from my original blog. It was my only post.&#xA;Before we begin: A game engine is a tool which is used to create games. It usually has a user interface and a scripting language (a specialized programming language unique to the engine) of some sort. A game _framework_ is a library of code which can be added to your code so it&amp;#39;s easier to make a game.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
